<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250821110129 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403626/20250821.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403626&amp;date=20250821&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821000000 +0000" stop="20250821030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">National Treasure</title>
    <desc>An adventurer (Nicolas Cage) must steal the Declaration of Independence and use its hidden map to find a legendary fortune.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821030000 +0000" stop="20250821040100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rainmaker</title>
    <desc>Fresh out of law school, Rudy Baylor confronts Leo F. Drummond in a medical malpractice case.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821040100 +0000" stop="20250821050100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Chief Boden leads the fight to keep the firehouse open; an emergency call to an apartment structure puts the squad in harm's way; Dawson receives life-changing news.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821050100 +0000" stop="20250821060100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey returns to work after a brush with death; Shay's new partner is friendly to everyone but her; Dawson begins training; Severide prepares for his instructor duties; Clarke refuses to talk to the police about the murder.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821060100 +0000" stop="20250821070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The detectives investigate when woman visiting from Buffalo, N.Y., claims her car was stolen with her baby in the backseat.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821070000 +0000" stop="20250821080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a young mail-order bride is found dead, the investigation leads the detectives to the Russian mafia.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821080000 +0000" stop="20250821090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives Benson and Rollins investigate when a mental patient says he witnessed a rape, but the alleged victim denies the assault happened.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821090000 +0000" stop="20250821100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a child disappears on his way home from school, Benson and Amaro interview the distraught parents, who don't trust the police; with the help of their TARU tech (Gilbert Gottfried) and a meddling reporter, the detectives narrow the suspects list.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821100000 +0000" stop="20250821110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>An elaborate bank heist to steal a single safe deposit box held by a Navy contractor leads NCIS to investigate her corrupt consulting firm.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821110000 +0000" stop="20250821120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>The NCIS team searches for a Marine reservist with a history of post-traumatic stress disorder who disappears following a drunk and disorderly altercation.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821120000 +0000" stop="20250821130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>The team investigates a possible terror threat after the chief of logistics for a naval weapons station collapses on the job; Kensi and Deeks research different honeymoon locations.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821130000 +0000" stop="20250821140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When the investigation into a missing teen leads the detectives to a severed leg, they are drawn into the world of self-mutilation and ritual amputation.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821140000 +0000" stop="20250821150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A promising singer is beaten by her boyfriend, a famous hip-hop star, but she refuses to help ADA Barba build his case; the defendant and his attorney turn the case into a media circus.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821150000 +0000" stop="20250821160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Investigation into the suspected rape of a woman Benson helped earlier leads to a cybermogul; the team bids farewell to Sgt. Munch.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821160000 +0000" stop="20250821170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>ADA Barba finds that a friend (Kirk Acevedo) -- with a connection to a mayoral candidate frontrunner -- is accused of rape.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821170000 +0000" stop="20250821180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a suspect is gravely injured and the case becomes a public spectacle, Amaro's badge is on the line; Cragen surprises everyone with an announcement.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821180000 +0000" stop="20250821190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When an underage runaway is found beaten and raped, the SVU team works with federal prosecutor Connie Rubirosa (Alana De La Garza); ADA Barba suspects a cover-up when he fails to get the help he needs from Jersey law enforcement.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821190000 +0000" stop="20250821200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Amaro suspects the boyfriend of a missing girl is involved with a gang; Sgt. Benson becomes the SVU's new commanding officer.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821200000 +0000" stop="20250821210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The already frantic search for a missing diabetic boy becomes more urgent when he is spotted with a couple known for child endangerment and pornography.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821210000 +0000" stop="20250821220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a controversial misogynistic comic is accused of rape, Benson is happy to arrest him, but Barba feels the case is weak.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821220000 +0000" stop="20250821230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detective Rollins is contacted by a hometown friend when his nephew, a high school football star, goes missing in New York; Rollins seeks help with her escalating problems.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821230000 +0000" stop="20250822000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When Rollins strikes a deal with the managers of a gambling club in order to protect her job, she ends up drawing the suspicion of Benson and Tutuola.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822000000 +0000" stop="20250822023200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">National Treasure: Book of Secrets</title>
    <desc>A page from the diary of John Wilkes Booth implicates Ben Gates' (Nicolas Cage) great-great grandfather as a major conspirator in the assassination of President Lincoln.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822023200 +0000" stop="20250822050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ticket to Paradise</title>
    <desc>A man and his ex-wife race to Bali, Indonesia, to stop their daughter from marrying a seaweed farmer. As they desperately try to sabotage the wedding, the bickering duo soon find themselves rekindling old feelings that once made them happy together.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822050000 +0000" stop="20250822060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When the investigation into a missing teen leads the detectives to a severed leg, they are drawn into the world of self-mutilation and ritual amputation.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822060000 +0000" stop="20250822070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A promising singer is beaten by her boyfriend, a famous hip-hop star, but she refuses to help ADA Barba build his case; the defendant and his attorney turn the case into a media circus.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822070000 +0000" stop="20250822080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Investigation into the suspected rape of a woman Benson helped earlier leads to a cybermogul; the team bids farewell to Sgt. Munch.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822080000 +0000" stop="20250822090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a suspect is gravely injured and the case becomes a public spectacle, Amaro's badge is on the line; Cragen surprises everyone with an announcement.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822090000 +0000" stop="20250822100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The already frantic search for a missing diabetic boy becomes more urgent when he is spotted with a couple known for child endangerment and pornography.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822100000 +0000" stop="20250822103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forensic Files</title>
    <desc>A clue no bigger than a thumbtack leads investigators to a trio of killers.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822103000 +0000" stop="20250822113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The first responders race to help a homeless man crushed in a garbage truck, a mother and son in a crashed elevator, and extreme hoarders trapped in their house; Athena starts dating; the situation with Abby's mother tests her relationship with Buck.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822113000 +0000" stop="20250822123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The first responders take calls involving an unusual domestic disturbance, a "death" at a psychic's place, and a motorcycle crash; Bobby dips his toes into the dating pool; Abby walks down memory lane, and Buck is confronted by his past actions.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822123000 +0000" stop="20250822133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>On one of the hottest days of the year, the first responders must deal with harrowing incidents all around the city; Buck gets a surprise visit from his sister; Athena questions her relationship with Bobby; Buck worries about a handsome new hire.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822133000 +0000" stop="20250822143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>A massive earthquake rocks Los Angeles; the first responders rush to rescue victims from a crumbling high-rise hotel; Athena must deal with wreckage from a collapsed freeway overpass; Maddie faces her first crisis as a 911 dispatcher.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822143000 +0000" stop="20250822153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The first responders continue to deal with the fallout of a massive earthquake; Athena tries to keep the peace as Bobby and team continue to rescue victims from a collapsing high-rise hotel; Maddie must help a pregnant couple deliver their baby.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822153000 +0000" stop="20250822163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The first responders race to rescue victims trapped in various tight spots; Athena contemplates accepting a promotion that will take her out of the field; Chimney finally deals with the aftermath of his near fatal car crash.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822163000 +0000" stop="20250822173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Maddie goes on a ride-along with Athena; Hen must figure out how to save her family from permanently falling apart; the first responders deal with emergencies both at a military funeral and a movie theater.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822173000 +0000" stop="20250822183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The first responders unwittingly become the subject of an eager reporter's first on-air assignment; Athena prepares for May's homecoming dance; the team responds to emergencies at an eating contest, a bodybuilding competition and a toddler pageant.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822183000 +0000" stop="20250822190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Premier League Mornings</title>
    <desc>Stateside Premier League fan festival that includes a turf pitch, the Premier League trophy, club mascots, special guests, contests, and more.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822190000 +0000" stop="20250822210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Premier League Soccer</title>
    <desc>The Hammers begin their home slate with a match against the Blues at London Stadium. West Ham started the season with a disappointing loss to recently-promoted Sunderland. Chelsea played to a nil-nil draw with Crystal Palace at Stamford Bridge.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822210000 +0000" stop="20250822213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Premier League Goal Zone</title>
    <desc>The best moments from the weekend in Premier League action.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822213000 +0000" stop="20250822220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forensic Files</title>
    <desc>In a wealthy area of Philadelphia, police are called to the scene of what seems like a regular accidental drowning; the investigation begins to focus on one person who has many reasons to want the victim dead.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822220000 +0000" stop="20250822230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A girl at Detective Stabler's daughter's school accuses another student of rape; ADA Paxton (Christine Lahti) returns to prosecute.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822230000 +0000" stop="20250823000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives Stabler and Tutuola search for a victim and her attacker after video of a sexual assault is featured on a college campus Intranet feed.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250823000000 +0000" stop="20250824000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WWE Friday Night SmackDown</title>
    <desc>The Superstars of World Wrestling Entertainment display their skills and athleticism in weekly episodic programming, as scores are settled and enduring rivalries play out in the ring.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-23</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
