<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250716100355 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403626/20250716.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403626&amp;date=20250716&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716000000 +0000" stop="20250716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Carisi and Rollins work together on an important arraignment; Benson tries to make Noah's Christmas wish come true when a case falls in her lap.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716010000 +0000" stop="20250716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When Benson becomes the target of a ruthless gang leader, Capt. Duarte takes the case; Fin works with the Bronx SVU to help clear its case backlog; Lt. Dixon offers to translate when a deaf student is raped.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716020000 +0000" stop="20250716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>While Benson tries to help the gang member who attacked her, Duarte reveals a shocking piece of evidence in the case; Fin is tasked with hiring new detectives for the Bronx SVU.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716030000 +0000" stop="20250716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>As Benson and Carisi put a vengeful crime boss on trial, Fin tries to help a woman who was drugged and left for dead; Velasco takes drastic action to get information from a witness.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716040000 +0000" stop="20250716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A car accident leads the detectives on a search for an ambulance driver assaulting his charges; Fin gives Detective Bruno a tour of Manhattan SVU.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716050000 +0000" stop="20250716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The search for the sexual abuser of a child leads the detectives to a wealthy toy mogul known for his generous hospitality toward children.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716060000 +0000" stop="20250716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A woman attempts to kidnap a child she believes is her daughter; while DNA tests are in progress, Benson traces the confusion about the child's origins back to a fertility doctor.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716070000 +0000" stop="20250716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives investigate when a baby is left abandoned with a note indicating the mother's kidnapping and quickly learn that she has been kidnapped by a copycat serial killer.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716080000 +0000" stop="20250716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A professor (Billy Campbell) accused of sexual assault volunteers to submit a DNA sample for testing, but the case turns into a he-said, she-said standoff.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716090000 +0000" stop="20250716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stabler and Fin investigate the brutal rape and murder of a prostitute, and the prime suspects turn out to be a group of teens suspected of re-enacting a favorite video game.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716100000 +0000" stop="20250716103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forensic Files</title>
    <desc>A man has no recollection of events after stabbing his wife and holding her head underwater in a swimming pool.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716103000 +0000" stop="20250716113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>As the team investigates a convenience store robbery, the evidence leads them to an unusual pair of suspects, revealing a dark personal drama and another potential victim; Burgess slowly makes strides tackling her past trauma.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716113000 +0000" stop="20250716123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Atwater's worlds collide when a shooting at the building he owns in Burnside leaves a child dead; Atwater must confront his relationship with his father, Lew, as the brutal case forces them together.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716123000 +0000" stop="20250716133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Upton is unwittingly drawn into a deadly betrayal and finds herself in a fight for her life; with minimal leads, Voight and the team scramble to find her before it's too late.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716133000 +0000" stop="20250716143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Torres finds himself in the midst of a murder case that hits close to home and threatens to expose his troubled past; as he struggles to reconcile his old life with his new one, Voight keeps a watchful eye.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716143000 +0000" stop="20250716153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>As Richard Beck's timeline for a deadly attack moves up and Samantha panics, Ruzek and the team scramble to get ahead of unprecedented disaster.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716153000 +0000" stop="20250716163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Tasked with shadowing a crisis prevention team, Upton finds her approach to policing at odds with the team's mental health clinician; Voight stands by Upton as she continues to struggle in her personal life.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716163000 +0000" stop="20250716173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Ruzek gets mixed up in a case after a late-night poker game is raided; afraid of becoming like his father, Ruzek struggles to stand down and allow Intelligence to carry out the investigation while he remains on leave.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716173000 +0000" stop="20250716183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Carver deals with the fallout of his arrest; Brett searches for closure with the baby she rescued; Capp weasels his way into the Firehouse 51 group chat.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716183000 +0000" stop="20250716193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Brett waits for life-changing news; Herrmann encounters a psychic with a grave warning on a call; Kidd finds a new lead on the Homeland Security case.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716193000 +0000" stop="20250716203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Mouch sets out to change his legacy and nickname; Ritter pushes Herrmann to see a doctor; Brett searches for the perfect wedding venue.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716203000 +0000" stop="20250716213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Julia spends a couple of days at 51; Boden's stepson, James, returns, desperate for Boden to help his mother; after a little girl starts a fire in her backyard, Kidd and her team decide to dig deeper.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716213000 +0000" stop="20250716223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>After their defibrillator malfunctions on a call, Brett and Violet search for answers; Herrmann tries to find the perfect home for his new recliner; a secret from Gibson's past comes to light.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250716223000 +0000" stop="20250717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Olympus Has Fallen</title>
    <desc>Disgraced Secret Service agent Mike Banning finds himself trapped inside the White House in the wake of a terrorist attack and works with national security to rescue the President from his kidnappers.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250717010000 +0000" stop="20250717030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">London Has Fallen</title>
    <desc>In London for the Prime Minister's funeral, Mike Banning is caught up in a plot to assassinate all the attending world leaders.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250717030000 +0000" stop="20250717040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kings Court</title>
    <desc>Celebrity Kings Tyson, Carlos and Thaddeus begin their quest for love with the first group of Queens.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250717040000 +0000" stop="20250717050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A dead newborn leads detectives to a dermatologist, then a serial pedophile.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250717050000 +0000" stop="20250717060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A video voyeur catches a sexual assault against a minor on tape, which changes the focus of the investigation as the detectives search for a pedophile.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250717060000 +0000" stop="20250717070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The detectives discover that a murdered teenage girl was a prostitute and had contracted HIV while working on a pornographic film, which leads them to her killer.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250717070000 +0000" stop="20250717080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A home invasion and kidnapping lead the SVU to a shocking discovery; Muncy tries to fit in with the squad.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250717080000 +0000" stop="20250717193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 Open Championship</title>
    <desc>The opening round of The 153rd Open gets underway at Royal Portrush Golf Club in Northern Ireland.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250717193000 +0000" stop="20250717220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Olympus Has Fallen</title>
    <desc>Disgraced Secret Service agent Mike Banning finds himself trapped inside the White House in the wake of a terrorist attack and works with national security to rescue the President from his kidnappers.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250717220000 +0000" stop="20250718000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">London Has Fallen</title>
    <desc>In London for the Prime Minister's funeral, Mike Banning is caught up in a plot to assassinate all the attending world leaders.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250718000000 +0000" stop="20250719000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Angel Has Fallen</title>
    <desc>Wrongfully accused of trying to kill the president, framed Secret Service agent Mike Banning must evade the FBI and his own agency to uncover the truth and save the country from imminent danger.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
