<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250617095717 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403626/20250617.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403626&amp;date=20250617&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617000000 +0000" stop="20250617010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An Alzheimer's patient claims she was raped, but her illness casts doubt on the case; Fin's sergeant orders come in.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617010000 +0000" stop="20250617020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>SVU investigates the sexual assault of a 15-year-old boy, but when he won't cooperate, they must find another way to uncover his perpetrator; Rollins reconnects with her ex, and Benson worries she isn't the Wonder Woman she used to be.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617020000 +0000" stop="20250617030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>SVU investigates the sexual assault of a 15-year-old boy, but when he won't cooperate, they must find another way to uncover his perpetrator; Rollins reconnects with her ex; Benson worries she isn't the Wonder Woman she used to be.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617030000 +0000" stop="20250617040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry and Asta work together to try and get something Harry desperately needs.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617040000 +0000" stop="20250617050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>SVU investigates the assault, murder and mutilation of a member of a women's empowerment group; Fin and Carisi wonder who the father of Rollins' baby is.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617050000 +0000" stop="20250617060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>SVU must unravel the mystery of a sexually assaulted young homeless woman who has a dual personality; when she goes missing after being assaulted, the team is challenged to uncover not only her identity but also her whereabouts.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617060000 +0000" stop="20250617070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A columnist who has been given access to the squad for a story declares a hate crime case a hoax, leaving the victim under media scrutiny and Benson fighting to get the case back on solid ground.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617070000 +0000" stop="20250617080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>When the mysterious death of a 23-year-old mother in New Mexico goes unsolved, her family searches for answers.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617080000 +0000" stop="20250617090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>A pair of double homicides in Nebraska, five years apart, lead police to fear a serial killer may be on the loose.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617090000 +0000" stop="20250617100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>A pair of double homicides in Nebraska, five years apart, leads police to fear a serial killer may be on the loose.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617100000 +0000" stop="20250617110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>The team gets a new lead in the mole investigation after an unknown assailant kills two men disguised as sheriff's deputies in front of Callen's home; Nell interviews a prison inmate who has information on the department's leak.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617110000 +0000" stop="20250617120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>NCIS looks into the disappearance of a Navy lieutenant commander who is working on foreign cyber threats with the NSA; the team celebrates the holidays.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617120000 +0000" stop="20250617130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>After a Navy reservist is killed protecting a city councilman, Sam goes under cover in a private security firm that has links to criminal organizations.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617130000 +0000" stop="20250617140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a female video game developer who has been receiving death threats refuses to delay the launch of her new game, the cops must work to protect her.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617140000 +0000" stop="20250617150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>While working under cover to bust a sex trafficking ring, Carisi meets a woman who embedded herself in the organization in hope of finding and saving her daughter; Sgt. Benson is faced with a life-changing revelation.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617150000 +0000" stop="20250617160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Barba's efforts to make an arrest in a case involving pornographic photos is stalled when several suspects come down with the measles; Amaro receives distressing news about his son.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617160000 +0000" stop="20250617170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Efforts to find an 8-year-old boy kidnapped for ransom are hindered by tension between the child's estranged parents; Sgt. Benson is asked to take the lieutenant's exam and officially become the leader of the squad.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617170000 +0000" stop="20250617180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When Johnny D (Charles Halford) is on trial for sex trafficking, rape, assault and kidnapping, Noah's adoption becomes involved with the case, causing Benson to fear for the child's future; a threat could permanently change the squad.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617180000 +0000" stop="20250617190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a 15-year-old who was part of a group of kids who put a transgender teen in the hospital is tried as an adult, the SVU team wonders whether the punishment fits the crime.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617190000 +0000" stop="20250617200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An unarmed black man is shot during the pursuit of a suspect, raising racial tensions; Barba must indict the three officers involved -- who claim they followed procedure.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617200000 +0000" stop="20250617210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>SVU investigates when a father and his two young children are stabbed to death in their home; when the motives of the culprit are uncovered, Benson finds herself having mixed feelings about the nature of the crime.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617210000 +0000" stop="20250617220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a waitress at a popular restaurant is sexually assaulted, SVU looks for the culprit at the top of the culinary food chain, but Benson and Stone hit a wall when it's time to prosecute.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617220000 +0000" stop="20250617230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stone asks Benson to investigate a sexual encounter from his past that he feels guilt and uncertainty about; Rollins considers a proposal from Doctor Al.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250617230000 +0000" stop="20250618000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The murder of an elusive, shy teenage author living a double life leads Benson and the rest of the SVU on an investigation that uncovers a situation beyond their wildest imaginations.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU investigates a he-said, she-said case when a woman crashes a wedding to accuse her therapist of sexual assault.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618010000 +0000" stop="20250618020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and the team work to uncover a pregnant teenager's secret when she refuses to name the baby's father.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618020000 +0000" stop="20250618030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and the SVU team help a teenage exchange student from Italy after she's assaulted by a cab driver.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618030000 +0000" stop="20250618040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU searches for two suspects that were spotted fleeing the scene after a Muslim woman was assaulted inside a synagogue; Benson is dismayed to find that Rob Miller is out on bail.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618040000 +0000" stop="20250618050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a teenager is found dead in the Hudson River, Lt. Benson suspects Rob Miller is behind the mysterious death but can't prove it; despite having only circumstantial evidence, ADA Stone takes the case to court before Miller can destroy more lives.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618050000 +0000" stop="20250618060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A serial predator targeting men in gay bars proves difficult to catch, until a celebrity comes forward with his story.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618060000 +0000" stop="20250618070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>While working under cover to bust a sex trafficking ring, Carisi meets a woman who embedded herself in the organization in hope of finding and saving her daughter; Sgt. Benson is faced with a life-changing revelation.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618070000 +0000" stop="20250618080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Efforts to find an 8-year-old boy kidnapped for ransom are hindered by tension between the child's estranged parents; Sgt. Benson is asked to take the lieutenant's exam and officially become the leader of the squad.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618080000 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When Johnny D (Charles Halford) is on trial for sex trafficking, rape, assault and kidnapping, Noah's adoption becomes involved with the case, causing Benson to fear for the child's future; a threat could permanently change the squad.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a 15-year-old who was part of a group of kids who put a transgender teen in the hospital is tried as an adult, the SVU team wonders whether the punishment fits the crime.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>With the FBI closing in on the Roy Walton investigation, Voight and Halstead strategize a way out; after a city bus driver is shot by a passenger, the team investigates a possible abduction.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>The team searches for a missing child in what turns out to be a very complicated case; Burgess and Ruzek are in for a shock when someone from Makayla's past comes forward.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618120000 +0000" stop="20250618130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Voight employs his new informant to help solve a tricky drug trafficking case; Atwater, who once again struggles to reconcile his personal and professional life, reaches a decision.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618130000 +0000" stop="20250618140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>The team works together to identify the head of the brutal Los Temidos gang; Voight dives deeper into his informant Anna Avalos' past when her undercover role is threatened.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618140000 +0000" stop="20250618150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>While out for a jog, Upton witnesses a horrible car crash and risks her own life to save the passengers; after learning more about the victims, the team must track down the man responsible for the brutal crash.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618150000 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>The team searches for a brutal killer with a signature modus operandi; Burgess and Ruzek double down in their fight to retain custody of Makayla.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>When a young man is shot outside the Cárabo Bakery, the team works to connect the shooting to bakery owner Javier Escano, who has been under surveillance; despite the increasing danger, Voight helps informant Anna Avalos get closer to their target.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618170000 +0000" stop="20250618180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Chief Hawkins goes above and beyond to help Brett and Violet with a problem; Kidd pursues an open lieutenant position; a blast from the past asks Mouch and Herrmann for a favor.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618180000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Following an injury in the aftermath of an industrial fire, Severide and Seager work together to investigate an anonymous tip; Kidd searches for the right person to fill the open spot on Truck 81; a possible new recruit to 51 gets tested at a call.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Cruz forms a bond with a young immigrant boy he meets while fighting an apartment fire; Squad makes plans to prank the newest member of their team; Hawkins and Violet struggle to keep their relationship a secret.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide and Kidd work with CPD regarding a suspicious car wreck; Hawkins and Violet's relationship is in jeopardy; Chloe and Cruz adjust to a new family dynamic.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618210000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Firehouse 51 must band together when one of its own is taken hostage.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beast</title>
    <desc>A father and his two teenage daughters find themselves hunted by a massive rogue lion intent on proving that the Savanna has but one apex predator.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250619000000 +0000" stop="20250620000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Black Panther</title>
    <desc>Black Panther's mettle as king gets tested when an old enemy draws him into a conflict that puts his nation and the world at risk. The king must soon rally his allies and release his full power to defeat his foes and secure the safety of his people.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-19</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
