<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250711100239 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403626/20250711.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403626&amp;date=20250711&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711000000 +0000" stop="20250711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A mother becomes Stabler and Benson's prime suspect in the poisoning of her child; Novak enlists Clark's assistance in obtaining evidence to remove a judge from the bench after his bias in two child abuse cases leads to a wrongful arrest.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711010000 +0000" stop="20250711040300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jurassic World Dominion</title>
    <desc>Four years after the destruction of Isla Nublar, Biosyn operatives attempt to track down Maisie Lockwood, while Dr Ellie Sattler investigates a genetically engineered swarm of giant insects.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711040300 +0000" stop="20250711050300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The McBee Dynasty: Real American Cowboys</title>
    <desc>Eldest brother Steven has a plan to save the farm from financial ruin, but younger brother Cole has his own idea on what's best.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711050300 +0000" stop="20250711060300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A boy, 5, is abducted from his bed in the middle of the night, prompting detectives to take a hard look at the boy's estranged father.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711060300 +0000" stop="20250711070200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A standoff in a motel on the Jersey Shore incites a pedophile to take detective Benson hostage.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711070200 +0000" stop="20250711080100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives investigate the murder of a gay man who was the poster boy for sexual re-education.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711080100 +0000" stop="20250711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>After a man's mutilation on the subway, detectives discover he has been abducting women for years and forcing them to live in his dungeon.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711090000 +0000" stop="20250711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stabler and Capt. Cragen search for suspects after a missing infant is discovered badly beaten in the bushes at a local park.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711100000 +0000" stop="20250711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 has a day from hell with a never-ending series of bizarre emergency calls; a man tapes himself to a freeway billboard; a restaurant manager destroys his own business; Eddie feels a spark with Christopher's former teacher.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711110000 +0000" stop="20250711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The members of the 118 rush to the site of a hit-and-run that leaves a familiar face in critical condition; with Buck's help, Athena investigates the case of a missing woman; Josh recalls an emergency in 2006 that led him to become a first responder.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711120000 +0000" stop="20250711130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>When a famous mystery writer dies, Athena, Bobby and the 118 respond to the chaos caused by a citywide manhunt for buried treasure the author left behind.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711130000 +0000" stop="20250711140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The members of the 118 make calls to save a bridezilla at a disastrous wedding; Hen plays medical detective when her mother falls ill; Eddie and Christopher receive a visit from Carla; Athena uncovers a secret Bobby has been hiding.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711140000 +0000" stop="20250711150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Athena and the 118 are on high alert when a sniper is targeting members of the LAFD; Maddie makes a life decision.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711150000 +0000" stop="20250711160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>A series of ransomware threats leads to emergencies for the 118, including a helicopter crash at a hospital and an air traffic control tower system failure; the case of the realtor serial rapist goes to trial.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711160000 +0000" stop="20250711170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 springs into action when a citywide blackout and a record heat wave causes mayhem in Los Angeles; Chimney confides in Hen about Maddie's condition; Athena's worst nightmare comes true.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711170000 +0000" stop="20250711180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>As the citywide blackout continues to cause mayhem in Los Angeles, Athena races to save her family from a tragedy; Eddie must make a difficult choice about his future; Maddie makes a life-changing decision.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711180000 +0000" stop="20250711190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>A truck crashes into a high school homecoming parade; Athena and Michael try to help Harry in the aftermath of his kidnapping; May is intimidated by a returning call center legend; Bobby gives a devastated Chimney advice regarding Maddie.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711190000 +0000" stop="20250711200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>A man over-exerts himself exercising; a groundskeeper is cut by his chainsaw; an explosion occurs at a retirement community; May gets an emergency call from a suicidal teen.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711200000 +0000" stop="20250711210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Responding to a fire at a prison, Bobby and the 118 find themselves trapped in a deadly riot.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250711210000 +0000" stop="20250712000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jurassic World Dominion</title>
    <desc>Four years after the destruction of Isla Nublar, Biosyn operatives attempt to track down Maisie Lockwood, while Dr Ellie Sattler investigates a genetically engineered swarm of giant insects.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712000000 +0000" stop="20250712020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WWE Friday Night SmackDown</title>
    <desc>The Superstars of World Wrestling Entertainment display their skills and athleticism in weekly episodic programming, as scores are settled and enduring rivalries play out in the ring.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712020000 +0000" stop="20250712030200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry is brought in front of The Galactic Housing Council to answer for his crimes.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712030200 +0000" stop="20250712040400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry is brought in front of The Galactic Housing Council to answer for his crimes.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712040400 +0000" stop="20250712050400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry struggles to find balance with his new human form.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712050400 +0000" stop="20250712060400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry is brought in front of The Galactic Housing Council to answer for his crimes.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712060400 +0000" stop="20250712070300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>When a San Diego woman who is near death arrives at an emergency room, the FBI and local law enforcement are called in to try to solve a medical mystery and a horrific crime.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712070300 +0000" stop="20250712080200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>A successful businesswoman and mother of three is found shot in her office; the investigation into her death leaves a family divided.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712080200 +0000" stop="20250712090100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>The murder of a California mother beloved by four men reopens a mystery surrounding another young woman's death that occurred decades earlier.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712090100 +0000" stop="20250712100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>The murder of a California mother beloved by four men reopens a mystery surrounding another young woman's death that occurred decades earlier.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712100000 +0000" stop="20250712110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>A fire breaks out in an accountant's office and a car crashes into a "living funeral"; Athena is shocked when a suspect dies in her custody minutes after she arrests him; Buck is attracted to a death doula; Maddie and Chimney are audited by the IRS.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712110000 +0000" stop="20250712120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 race to rescue two roommates desperately trying to find a needle in a haystack at a landfill, and help a woman whose nightmare dream suddenly becomes a painful reality; Athena and Maddie team up to find a missing boy in a crowded mall.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712120000 +0000" stop="20250712130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>A wedding proposal tragically intersects with a bank robbery; a bride is literally stuck on her way to the altar; Athena talks a victim through her grief; Buck finds a surprise visitor on his doorstep.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712130000 +0000" stop="20250712140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>A series of freeway car accidents leads to a catastrophic overpass collapse that endangers the lives of civilians and members of the 118.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712140000 +0000" stop="20250712150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Athena and Bobby set off on their honeymoon cruise, but when duty calls, their vacation is put on hold; a fighter jet traps a civilian; an unusual incident leaves a couple stuck together.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712150000 +0000" stop="20250712160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The disastrous cruise continues when Bobby and Athena respond to the ship's explosion, racing to aid injured passengers; Hen questions her instincts in a life-taking call and grows concerned about Athena and Bobby's whereabouts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712160000 +0000" stop="20250712170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>With each moment becoming critical as the ship flips upside down, Athena and Bobby take charge, seeking methods for rescue while navigating efforts to guide survivors to safety; Hen defies protocols in her search for Bobby and Athena.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712170000 +0000" stop="20250712193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hall Pass</title>
    <desc>Rick and Fred, two husbands who are having difficulty in their marriages, are given a Hall Pass by their wives for one week, they can do whatever they want.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712193000 +0000" stop="20250712220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Talladega Nights: The Ballad of Ricky Bobby</title>
    <desc>NASCAR driver Ricky Bobby faces his greatest challenge ever when French Formula One driver Jean Girard roars onto the scene.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712220000 +0000" stop="20250712223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>The Dunder Mifflin employees suffer through the annual office awards ceremony, The Dundies, hosted by Michael at their local watering hole a Chili's restaurant.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712223000 +0000" stop="20250712230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>Corporate office requires the staff go through sexual harassment training, but Michael worries that the new policy will make the office less fun for everyone.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712230000 +0000" stop="20250712233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>While Michael and Dwight are away from the office, Jim and Pam organize an office Olympics where employees compete in ridiculous games.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250712233000 +0000" stop="20250713000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>A small fire in the kitchen forces the staff to wait in the parking lot; Jim suggests a game of Desert Island; Michael tries to impress Ryan.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250713000000 +0000" stop="20250714000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>Halloween is not much fun for Michael when he learns he must fire someone; Jim and Pam put Dwight's CV on the internet.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-13</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
