<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250625092723 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403626/20250625.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403626&amp;date=20250625&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625000000 +0000" stop="20250625010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Rollins goes under cover to find a suspect who is drugging and assaulting tourists, while Benson helps the victims sort out their memories from their hallucinations.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625010000 +0000" stop="20250625020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson investigates a police officer's accusations of sexual assault; Capt. Tucker's retirement party ends in tragedy.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625020000 +0000" stop="20250625030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Kat steps over the line when she suspects a trainer at her boxing gym is taking advantage of his students.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625030000 +0000" stop="20250625040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Rollins tries to root out a government worker who is withholding green cards in exchange for sex.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625040000 +0000" stop="20250625050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The female CEO of a popular wellness company says she was raped, but her business partner claims the accusation is part of an embezzlement cover-up.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625050000 +0000" stop="20250625060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An ingénue ballerina discovers she's been secretly videotaped for a pornographic website.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625060000 +0000" stop="20250625070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The detectives must solve a 5-year-old sexual assault case before the statute of limitations closes it.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625070000 +0000" stop="20250625080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A sexual assault case involving a teenage girl leads Benson and Stabler to set up a sting operation to trap Internet pedophiles.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625080000 +0000" stop="20250625090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The trial of an accused child molester is jeopardized when the prime witness has difficulty dealing with his past.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625090000 +0000" stop="20250625100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stabler's daughter bears witness to a horrific crime scene; the internal investigation into the psyches of the SVU detectives yields interesting results.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625100000 +0000" stop="20250625110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Ruzek's search for the daughter of an old family friend leads the team into a serious drug investigation; Burgess and Ruzek struggle to move on from the emotional aftermath of Makayla's abduction.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625110000 +0000" stop="20250625120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Halstead takes a new recruit under his wing during an investigation; the dynamics are challenging, however, and questions arise over the recruit's complicated past.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625120000 +0000" stop="20250625130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>After the murder of a wealthy Chicago man, Atwater and the team dig in to uncover the truth, suspecting there is more to the story than meets the eye.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625130000 +0000" stop="20250625140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>As the team closes in on drug kingpin Javier Escano, Voight is forced to lie to his undercover informant Anna to keep her on track; their deteriorating trust threatens an increasingly tenuous operation.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625140000 +0000" stop="20250625150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>After an explosion rocks the case, the team scrambles to finally take down Escano as everyone nears their breaking point.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625150000 +0000" stop="20250625160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Still reeling from the death of informant Anna, Voight faces a new threat as he tries to keep the neighborhood clean; new wrinkles develop in the Upton, Halstead and Voight dynamic; the team gets a new chief.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625160000 +0000" stop="20250625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>When a convicted murderer hijacks a prison van, the team scrambles to find him and the abducted prison guard before it's too late; Burgess questions Ruzek's motives in a case, creating tension between the two.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625170000 +0000" stop="20250625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Firehouse 51 tackles a fire caused by a dropped jet engine, and one of their own is accused of a theft related to the incident; Kidd and Boden disapprove of Kylie's potential new love interest.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625180000 +0000" stop="20250625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>A family friend asks Herrmann for some advice on opening a bar; tensions run high between Emma and Violet; Kidd struggles to keep her team together.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625190000 +0000" stop="20250625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Mouch and Ritter work together to solve a murder mystery; Severide and Cruz tackle a food truck fire; Gallo goes to see Hawkins about Violet.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625200000 +0000" stop="20250625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>The big wedding day arrives and Firehouse 51 welcomes Casey back to celebrate the joyous occasion; Emma's plans to replace Violet come to a shocking end.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625210000 +0000" stop="20250625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Kidd and Severide's honeymoon is interrupted by a dangerous person from their past; Kidd's former academy classmate joins Firehouse 51; Brett and Violet reflect on their relationships.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625220000 +0000" stop="20250625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Javi spends a couple of shifts at Firehouse 51; Kidd and Carver work together to help Carver's former boss; as Hawkins and Violet's relationship blossoms, Gallo turns his attention elsewhere.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250625230000 +0000" stop="20250626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Kidd recruits Carver, Capp and Tony to help prepare her new lieutenant's quarters; Severide and Detective Pryma reluctantly pair up to work a police investigation; Firehouse 51 comes together to fight a movie theater fire.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626000000 +0000" stop="20250626033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Black Panther: Wakanda Forever</title>
    <desc>Queen Ramonda, Shuri, M'Baku, Okoye and the Dora Milaje fight to protect their nation from intervening world powers in the wake of King T'Challa's death.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626033000 +0000" stop="20250626043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry and D'arcy travel to an unexpected place to recover an alien device left behind by his people.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626043000 +0000" stop="20250626053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An abused 7-year-old girl lies comatose while Benson and Stabler try to figure out which member of her dysfunctional family is responsible for her state.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626053000 +0000" stop="20250626063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The shooting death of a school student by a 7-year-old classmate leads to new information on an unsolved slaying.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626063000 +0000" stop="20250626073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Rollins clashes with the parents of a teenage runaway; the squad comes together for a significant event.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626073000 +0000" stop="20250626083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The detectives are spread thin when three major cases come in at midnight; Rollins and Carisi argue over an arrest.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626083000 +0000" stop="20250626093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU joins an under cover task force in busting a human trafficking ring.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626093000 +0000" stop="20250626100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forensic Files</title>
    <desc>Three seemingly unrelated deaths proved to be serial murders; the killer had been careful, he uses poison which had no taste or odour, fortunately for investigators, it also has a unique chemical signature.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626100000 +0000" stop="20250626110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>Callen and Sam go under cover to track an engineer attempting to sell classified information; Deeks plans a surprise for Kensi and her friends.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626110000 +0000" stop="20250626120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>The team investigates when a defense contractor designing a nuclear attack weapon is suspected, by her husband, of selling Navy secrets to a foreign government.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626120000 +0000" stop="20250626130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>The NCIS team must work with Hetty's former Vietnam War colleagues after a highly decorated Navy captain kidnaps a Veterans Affairs administrator who has been siphoning funds.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626130000 +0000" stop="20250626140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The truth behind the alleged rape of a woman by her police officer husband comes to light when a history of domestic abuse is uncovered.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626140000 +0000" stop="20250626150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An abused 7-year-old girl lies comatose while Benson and Stabler try to figure out which member of her dysfunctional family is responsible for her state.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626150000 +0000" stop="20250626160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The shooting death of a school student by a 7-year-old classmate leads to new information on an unsolved slaying.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626160000 +0000" stop="20250626170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The detectives probe the backgrounds of the family of a 17-year-old girl who was raped during a hotel-opening gala.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626170000 +0000" stop="20250626180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The detectives investigate the celebrity parents of a boy who killed himself by running into oncoming traffic.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626180000 +0000" stop="20250626190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A cop-turned-activist (Eric Roberts) becomes a suspect in the killings of several rapists who were recently paroled.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626190000 +0000" stop="20250626200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The rape of a veteran police officer is first linked to her ex-husband's gambling debts, and then to her fellow officers.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626200000 +0000" stop="20250626210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and Stabler take over the search for a runaway girl and are led to an underground rave culture that caters to wayward teens.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626210000 +0000" stop="20250626220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The beating of a young man uncovers a dangerous male escort service where the boss may have reasons for sending her staff on potentially deadly dates.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626220000 +0000" stop="20250626230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The details of a kidnapping are similar to a series of rapes and murders that may link the crime to a serial killer.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250626230000 +0000" stop="20250627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When the detectives investigate the death of a Romanian immigrant, suspicions surface that she is alive and masquerading as her twin.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250627000000 +0000" stop="20250628000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Black Panther</title>
    <desc>Black Panther's mettle as king gets tested when an old enemy draws him into a conflict that puts his nation and the world at risk. The king must soon rally his allies and release his full power to defeat his foes and secure the safety of his people.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-27</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
