<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250730100736 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403626/20250730.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403626&amp;date=20250730&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730000000 +0000" stop="20250730010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A doctor arrested for sexually abusing his patients is set free after Cassidy's testimony causes a mistrial.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730010000 +0000" stop="20250730020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A girl's tragic death becomes a criminal case when a surgeon harvests her organs without parental consent.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730020000 +0000" stop="20250730030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A 10-year-old girl taken from her mother at the U.S.-Mexico border ends up in a sex-trafficking ring in New York, and Benson and Stone fight to reunite the girl with her mother; Rollins confesses to her ex.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730030000 +0000" stop="20250730040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A serial rapist strikes again after two decades of silence, and SVU is determined to uncover the elusive criminal and bring justice to his many victims; Stone discovers that his father worked on the case before it went cold.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730040000 +0000" stop="20250730050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and the team investigate the death of a prostitute at a brothel; they wonder if there was foul play or if this could be a case of a junkie who relapsed, turned to tricking, got depressed and committed suicide.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730050000 +0000" stop="20250730060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A bitter separation pits a husband and wife (Blair Underwood, Michael Michele) against each other as they try to gain custody of their daughter (Tiffany Evans).</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730060000 +0000" stop="20250730070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Fin is asked to look into a case of rape at his son's college, where he meets a Brooklyn detective (Adam Beach) who is investigating a similar crime.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730070000 +0000" stop="20250730080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a mob lawyer (Cary Elwes) and his wife are attacked, their young son is the only witness; when he comes out of surgery, the man vividly remembers his daughter at the crime scene.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730080000 +0000" stop="20250730090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An overzealous reporter's accusation leads a despondent new mother (Ashley Williams) to kill herself; detectives continue to search for the mother's missing child as time gets shorter.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730090000 +0000" stop="20250730100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>After a female pundit is assaulted during a protest, Benson and Barba struggle to put their political beliefs aside to help bring the attacker to justice.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730100000 +0000" stop="20250730110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>When District 21 goes after a Colombian drug gang following a series of brutal slayings, an asset in the investigation emerges.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730110000 +0000" stop="20250730120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Antonio believes a Colombian gang is involved in his son's kidnapping; Halstead learns new information about Lindsay; Voight offers Antonio a new way to get information about Diego's whereabouts.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730120000 +0000" stop="20250730130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Voight and the team check out a house that has been associated with a series of gangs; people from the past cause Halstead's temper to rise.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730130000 +0000" stop="20250730140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Olinsky tries to protect his daughter; a counterfeiting operation is investigated; when a hoarder is arrested, more than clutter is uncovered.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730140000 +0000" stop="20250730150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Atwater and Burgess must keep their new patrol car in mint condition; the Intelligence Unit uncovers drug smuggling; Voight's behavior toward Lindsay drives her right where he doesn't want her; tensions rise between Olinsky and Ruzek.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730150000 +0000" stop="20250730160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>New York's SVU agents Fin and Rollins help track down a serial killer who rapes his victims; Burgess gets an opportunity to prove herself; Lindsay brings Halstead as her date to her high school reunion.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730160000 +0000" stop="20250730170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Voight's son may be involved with the Fitori murder case, intensifying tension between Antonio and Voight; Ruzek helps Burgess get retribution.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730170000 +0000" stop="20250730180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>The Firehouse 51 crew has a Thanksgiving to remember when drugs, a car accident, and a gang shooting get in the way of traditional holiday pastimes.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730180000 +0000" stop="20250730190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Peter is deeply upset when a young victim is discovered at the site of a train accident; an abusive mother takes dire actions; Severide's injury is aggravated.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730190000 +0000" stop="20250730200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Jose Vargas is forced to go on disability after sustaining an injury in a fire; Severide receives a tempting invitation from a woman he saved from a car crash; Cruz tries to end his brother's involvement with a gang.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730200000 +0000" stop="20250730210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>An expensive necklace goes missing at the scene of a fire, leading to an internal investigation; Cruz makes a desperate decision to save his brother from a gang war; Dawson invites Casey to a party.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730210000 +0000" stop="20250730220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Cruz struggles with guilt and decides to make a confession to Casey; Severide asks Dawson for help with his injury; Herrmann is faced with an unpleasant business deal.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730220000 +0000" stop="20250730230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide finally decides to discuss his injury with Chief Boden; Casey deals with family issues; Dawson responds to a rescue call and realizes a young girl is the only survivor.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250730230000 +0000" stop="20250731000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rock</title>
    <desc>A scientist (Nicolas Cage) and a British spy (Sean Connery) who once escaped from Alcatraz are sent to the former island prison to stop a disgruntled war hero (Ed Harris) from obliterating San Francisco with chemical warheads.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250731020000 +0000" stop="20250731050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rock</title>
    <desc>A scientist (Nicolas Cage) and a British spy (Sean Connery) who once escaped from Alcatraz are sent to the former island prison to stop a disgruntled war hero (Ed Harris) from obliterating San Francisco with chemical warheads.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250731050000 +0000" stop="20250731060200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry enlists an unlikely ally to help him save Patience.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250731060200 +0000" stop="20250731070100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A successful preacher (Tim Daly) is the prime suspect in a murder case, until his wife (Kathy Baker) provides detectives with a taped conversation.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250731070100 +0000" stop="20250731080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The only witness to the beating of a woman (Judy Kuhn) is her daughter (Paulina Gerzon) who has Williams syndrome.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250731080000 +0000" stop="20250731090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives discover a kidnapped girl in the trunk of a stolen rental car; the suspect's rage seriously injures Stabler; the trial forces Novak to face dark things in her past.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250731090000 +0000" stop="20250731100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When an infant goes missing, members of the SVU find themselves taking sides in a family's right-to-die court case; Barba's interference in the case puts the entire DA's office in jeopardy.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250731100000 +0000" stop="20250731110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry enlists an unlikely ally to help him save Patience.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250731110000 +0000" stop="20250731180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 AIG Women's Open</title>
    <desc>Watch the opening round of the AIG Women's Open at Royal Porthcawl Golf Club in Porthcawl, Wales.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250731180000 +0000" stop="20250731190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a polygamist's wife is murdered, he fears his testimony in a separate case may have led to her death; a Web site exposes potential witnesses.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250731190000 +0000" stop="20250731200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A wealthy teen is found murdered in New York's Central Park, and the clues lead to a gang of homeless children.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250731200000 +0000" stop="20250731210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A woman's body is found in a park alongside a man with a bullet in his head.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250731210000 +0000" stop="20250731220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The case of a teenage girl assaulted in the projects leads to a startling discovery; Benson puts her trust in someone from her past.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250731220000 +0000" stop="20250731230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Amaro asks the SVU for help in clearing a convicted man's name and brings a figure from Benson's past back into her life.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250731230000 +0000" stop="20250801000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a popular fighter doesn't show up for the biggest bout of the year, Rollins and Velasco are drawn into a complicated web of secrets; McGrath confides in Benson.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250801000000 +0000" stop="20250802000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Carisi's niece helps a friend report a sexual assault; Benson investigates a college's secret society that preys on female students.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-01</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
