<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250620095627 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403626/20250620.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403626&amp;date=20250620&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620000000 +0000" stop="20250620030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Independence Day</title>
    <desc>When alien invaders lay waste to planet Earth, it's up to a select group of survivors to make a last-ditch stand.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620030000 +0000" stop="20250620053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serenity</title>
    <desc>Crew members (Nathan Fillion, Gina Torres, Alan Tudyk) aboard a transport vessel get caught in a deadly conflict in the wake of a galactic war.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620053000 +0000" stop="20250620063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry and Asta work together to try and get something Harry desperately needs.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620063000 +0000" stop="20250620073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A teenager is sexually assaulted and left for dead in an alley after attending a movie star's party; Benson is suspicious when security footage from the party goes missing.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620073000 +0000" stop="20250620083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A woman wants to recant her testimony and free her father, who was incarcerated for incest and rape when she was a child; Capt. Cragen, who remembers the original investigation, tries to help the team.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620083000 +0000" stop="20250620093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Rollins' mother throws her a baby shower; the team's investigation into the rape of a violinist by her colleague leads to Rollins' fugitive sister; Sgt. Mike Dodds reports for his first day.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620093000 +0000" stop="20250620100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forensic Files</title>
    <desc>A teenager goes missing after an evening of horseback riding; her body is found a month later, three miles from her home; the killer unknowingly leaves a trace of evidence behind, tiny but unmistakable clues that pointed to him and him alone.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620100000 +0000" stop="20250620103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forensic Files</title>
    <desc>When a popular disc jockey is found murdered in a community garden, police swing into action; a sniffer dog and a blood spatter expert led police to the killer and he'd been much closer than they realize.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620103000 +0000" stop="20250620113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Athena and the 118 respond to bizarre emergency calls on Halloween, including a flock of crows terrorizing a field trip, an office employee having a close encounter with an eight-limbed creature and a ghost-like girl wandering a neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620113000 +0000" stop="20250620123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>When a murder weapon from a case close to Athena in the early '90s resurfaces, flashbacks to 1989 show how Athena joined the LAPD and became the police officer she is today.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620123000 +0000" stop="20250620133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Holiday-themed incidents include a shopper pushed over the edge, a woman who is literally having a "Blue Christmas" and a luggage handler accident on a tarmac; Maddie revisits her past to embrace her future; Bobby receives shocking news.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620133000 +0000" stop="20250620143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 responds to a skydiving trip gone wrong; a bank rep is injured in a home repossession; a lovestruck assistant's lunch run ends in disaster; Athena and the family come to terms with Michael's difficult health decision.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620143000 +0000" stop="20250620153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 responds to a viral stunt gone haywire, a disaster at a couple's fishing trip and an epic first date fail; Athena investigates a woman who doesn't remember being shot in the head; Eddie must have a difficult conversation with Christopher.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620153000 +0000" stop="20250620163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Accidents happen at a bowling alley and a home renovation; Athena pursues a car thief; Bobby and Michael take Harry camping; Chimney and Maddie rush into action when their romantic dinner date takes a wild turn.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620163000 +0000" stop="20250620173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Maddie fears for herself and her co-workers when the call center is taken hostage.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620173000 +0000" stop="20250620183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Eddie's journey to rescue a boy from a well turns into a mission to save himself from his past.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620183000 +0000" stop="20250620210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Serenity</title>
    <desc>Crew members (Nathan Fillion, Gina Torres, Alan Tudyk) aboard a transport vessel get caught in a deadly conflict in the wake of a galactic war.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250620210000 +0000" stop="20250621000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Independence Day</title>
    <desc>When alien invaders lay waste to planet Earth, it's up to a select group of survivors to make a last-ditch stand.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621000000 +0000" stop="20250621030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WWE Friday Night SmackDown</title>
    <desc>The Superstars of World Wrestling Entertainment display their skills and athleticism in weekly episodic programming, as scores are settled and enduring rivalries play out in the ring.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621030000 +0000" stop="20250621040200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry and D'arcy travel to an unexpected place to recover an alien device left behind by his people.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621040200 +0000" stop="20250621050200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Athena and the 118 respond to bizarre emergency calls on Halloween, including a flock of crows terrorizing a field trip, an office employee having a close encounter with an eight-limbed creature and a ghost-like girl wandering a neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621050200 +0000" stop="20250621060200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>When a murder weapon from a case close to Athena in the early '90s resurfaces, flashbacks to 1989 show how Athena joined the LAPD and became the police officer she is today.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621060200 +0000" stop="20250621070200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry and D'arcy travel to an unexpected place to recover an alien device left behind by his people.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621070200 +0000" stop="20250621080100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>When Ohio mother Heather Bogle goes missing, a detective identifies multiple suspects, until he himself comes under scrutiny for his investigation.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621080100 +0000" stop="20250621090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>The investigation into the death of a woman whose remains were found in her Frisco, Texas, garage leads detectives to a series of suspects with connections to the victim's complicated and secretive life.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621090000 +0000" stop="20250621100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>The investigation into the death of a woman whose remains were found in her Frisco, Texas, garage leads detectives to a series of suspects with connections to the victim's complicated and secretive life.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621100000 +0000" stop="20250621110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Firehouse 51 bands together to fight a raging fire on the 20th floor of the residential high-rise where Jay and Will Halstead's father lives and has gone missing; in the midst of the chaos, Brett learns unsettling information about her new partner.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621110000 +0000" stop="20250621120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide investigates a victim's motives after rescuing him and his child from a car accident; Boden clashes with Gorsch over appointing a new lieutenant; Mouch reaches out to a fellow firefighter; Cruz discovers he has a new admirer.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621120000 +0000" stop="20250621130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Herrmann faces hazing in his new role as lieutenant; Foster suspects a young gymnast's injury is more than meets the eye; Severide is jealous of Kidd's best friend; Casey and Boden turn to P.D. after treating two victims who have similar injuries.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621130000 +0000" stop="20250621140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Foster faces blowback after pointing out a doctor's oversight; Brett helps Casey look for a new apartment; Kidd prepares Tuesday the Dalmatian for the Fire Safety Dog Competition; a serious accusation is leveled against Severide.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621140000 +0000" stop="20250621150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey struggles to get Boden to sign off on an energetic new recruit; Foster extends an olive branch to her irritating new medic; Otis inspires Herrmann to seek new partners at Molly's; Brett realizes life in Fowlerton will take some getting used to.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621150000 +0000" stop="20250621160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Tension builds when a group of rabble-rousers attempts to lock down the firehouse; Brett is faced with a monumental decision; Cruz readies himself for a big day; Gallo and Ritter attempt to launch Firehouse 51 into the social media age.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621160000 +0000" stop="20250621170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>A series of false alarms at a private school hinders 51's ability to respond to legitimate emergencies; Kidd asks for ideas to surprise Severide on his birthday; Cruz and Brett rent out their extra room but get more than they bargained for.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621170000 +0000" stop="20250621180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Brett and Mackey find their lives in peril; Casey and Brett tread in unfamiliar territory; Severide chases a memory while Kidd adeptly solves a firehouse problem; Ritter puts himself in harm's way during a harrowing call.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621180000 +0000" stop="20250621190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>A fire at a homeless encampment leaves Severide and Casey searching for answers; Cruz is shaken up after a close call; Ritter lends a helping hand to a victim.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621190000 +0000" stop="20250621200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide and Casey try to find the best fit for Kidd; Ritter, Gallo and Violet help plan an event for Mouch.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621200000 +0000" stop="20250621210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Firehouse 51 deals with the aftermath of the capsized boat rescue; Gallo, Ritter and Violet discuss plans for a side gig.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621210000 +0000" stop="20250621220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Griffin learns the truth about his father's death and reveals why he really came to visit Casey; Gallo, Ritter and Violet take steps to expand their microbrewery business.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621220000 +0000" stop="20250621230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Kidd spreads her wings as a lieutenant; Chief Hawkins rides with Ambulance 61 to learn more about Brett; Casey takes a trip out of town; a Ritter date night turns into an emergency situation.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250621230000 +0000" stop="20250622000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey makes a life-altering decision; Gallo, Ritter and Violet agree to an interview and photo shoot; Brett and Mouch launch the paramedicine program; Cruz comes closer to fatherhood.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250622000000 +0000" stop="20250623000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>A major security breach in the city's computer networks forces Firehouse 51's senior leaders to take matters into their own hands; Severide gears up for an arson investigation.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-22</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
