<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250612095533 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403626/20250612.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403626&amp;date=20250612&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612000000 +0000" stop="20250612023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Mummy</title>
    <desc>An ancient Egyptian princess is awakened from her crypt beneath the desert, bringing with her malevolence grown over millennia, and terrors that defy human comprehension.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612023000 +0000" stop="20250612050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Twister</title>
    <desc>Storm-chasers (Helen Hunt, Bill Paxton) finalizing their divorce try to place equipment inside a tornado on the Oklahoma plains.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612050000 +0000" stop="20250612060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry must escape an outer space prison to stop a dangerous threat in town.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612060000 +0000" stop="20250612070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When Rollins strikes a deal with the managers of a gambling club in order to protect her job, she ends up drawing the suspicion of Benson and Tutuola.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612070000 +0000" stop="20250612080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson is assigned a 24/7 security detail when William Lewis (Pablo Schreiber) escapes from prison and starts killing again; Benson must decide how much she is willing to sacrifice to save a child's life.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612080000 +0000" stop="20250612090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Sgt. Olivia Benson is investigated by Internal Affairs after William Lewis' death; as pressure mounts, Olivia has to choose between her convictions and her badge.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612090000 +0000" stop="20250612100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A teenager disappears after schoolmates make her the subject of a vicious cyberbullying attack.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612100000 +0000" stop="20250612103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forensic Files</title>
    <desc>Two women are murdered in the same town and police fear a serial killer is on the loose, further investigation finds that they were both close to the same man.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612103000 +0000" stop="20250612210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 U.S. Open Golf Championship</title>
    <desc>From Oakmont Country Club in Oakmont, Pa.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612210000 +0000" stop="20250612233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Mummy</title>
    <desc>An ancient Egyptian princess is awakened from her crypt beneath the desert, bringing with her malevolence grown over millennia, and terrors that defy human comprehension.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612233000 +0000" stop="20250613000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Twister</title>
    <desc>Storm-chasers (Helen Hunt, Bill Paxton) finalizing their divorce try to place equipment inside a tornado on the Oklahoma plains.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613020000 +0000" stop="20250613030500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Revival</title>
    <desc>As the dead return to life in a small town, Officer Dana Cypress unearths a new deadly mystery.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613030500 +0000" stop="20250613040600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry must escape an outer space prison to stop a dangerous threat in town.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613040600 +0000" stop="20250613050600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a student disappears during a school trip to New York, the cops race to find a mysterious masked man; Fin and Stone both get visits from family.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613050600 +0000" stop="20250613060600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU must break through military red tape when a soldier is suspected of sexual assault.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613060600 +0000" stop="20250613070500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An old kidnapping case is reopened when a young woman is found wandering in Central Park; Carisi's conversation with a reporter puts him in hot water.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613070500 +0000" stop="20250613080400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a teenage girl is found dead, Rollins goes under cover at a high-end rehab center where the victim was last seen; Benson tries to overcome her doubts about Sheila.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613080400 +0000" stop="20250613090200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson must disclose the secrets of her past to help a rape victim recall the details of one terrible, traumatic night.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613090200 +0000" stop="20250613100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Rollins races to rescue a girl being held captive by her father.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613100000 +0000" stop="20250613110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>A skating mishap at an ice show; an accident involving a self-driving car; a fulfillment warehouse robot goes rogue; Eddie's after-hours fight club gets out of control; Hen struggles in her relationship with Karen.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613110000 +0000" stop="20250613120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 responds to debris from a meteor shower crashing into an apartment building and a deadly fire caused by a hazardous waste truck crash; Hen struggles with guilt over her ambulance accident; Bobby introduces Eddie to an old friend.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613120000 +0000" stop="20250613130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 races to rescue a little girl in a runaway hot air balloon and help with a city power outage caused by a hijacked tree-trimmer truck; Athena's investigation into the serial rapist case puts her life in jeopardy.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613130000 +0000" stop="20250613140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 rush to save lives in the aftermath of a massive train derailment.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613140000 +0000" stop="20250613150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>When the Hollywood Reservoir dam breaks, Bobby and the 118 race into action to save passengers on a city bus that has crashed into a building several stories in the air; the team adjusts to life as first responders during the pandemic.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613150000 +0000" stop="20250613160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>In the aftermath of the dam break, massive mudslides wreak havoc throughout Los Angeles; Athena fights to save herself and an agoraphobic woman after her house collapses; a group of pregnant women trapped in a submerged house.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613160000 +0000" stop="20250613170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The team races to save a man under siege by his high-tech smart home; a yoga teacher loses her vision; Athena hunts down a bank robber disguised by COVID-19 protocols; members of the 118's crew prepare for an out-of-state mission.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613170000 +0000" stop="20250613180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>A man gets pinned under a Humvee; a garage band rocks out too hard; Michael notices strange behavior at a nearby apartment; Hen's mother unexpectedly arrives and announces she is moving to Los Angeles.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613180000 +0000" stop="20250613190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Athena and the 118 race to save lives after a drunken driver causes a deadly pileup on the freeway; Maddie goes into labor; Hen and Karen are devastated as they prepare their foster daughter to be reunited with her birth mother.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613190000 +0000" stop="20250613200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 responds to calls dealing with parents and their children, including a disastrous birthday party thrown by a mommy blogger; Athena and Michael talk to May about her past suicide attempt; Chimney and Maddie adjust to life with their newborn.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613200000 +0000" stop="20250613210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>A social media influencer has an accident in a sauna; an emergency at a reality show wedding; a tragedy when a mother and her daughter go hiking; Maddie worries she has missed too many firsts with Jee-Yun.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613210000 +0000" stop="20250613220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 races to the rescue when the call center goes up in flames; Bobby risks his life to save a trapped May and Claudette; Buck and Eddie must help an injured electrician; Chimney and his brother team up as firefighters for the first time.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613220000 +0000" stop="20250613230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>After a mysterious death, Hen and Chimney put their lives in danger when they suspect that someone is playing God to make themselves look like a hero; Eddie visits Texas, where he attempts to reconcile with his father.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250613230000 +0000" stop="20250614000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Members of the 118 attempt to rescue a wellness retreat guru after his followers turn on him; an emergency call at an upscale hair salon; Maddie contemplates returning to work, Eddie and May make decisions about their future.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250614000000 +0000" stop="20250615000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WWE Friday Night SmackDown</title>
    <desc>The Superstars of World Wrestling Entertainment display their skills and athleticism in weekly episodic programming, as scores are settled and enduring rivalries play out in the ring.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-14</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
