<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250708095836 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403626/20250708.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403626&amp;date=20250708&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708000000 +0000" stop="20250708010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a teenage sex worker disappears, Rollins and Velasco find a key clue in a pile of neglected missing persons reports.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708010000 +0000" stop="20250708020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Carisi asks the SVU for help with a murder investigation when one of the witnesses shows signs of abuse.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708020000 +0000" stop="20250708030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Carisi tries Richard Wheatley for the murder of Kathy Stabler; Benson finds herself at odds with a friend when Barba agrees to take the case.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708030000 +0000" stop="20250708040200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry struggles to find balance with his new human form.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708040200 +0000" stop="20250708050200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The death of a boy and his abusive guardian leads the detectives to a travel agency specializing in exotic trips for sexual predators.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708050200 +0000" stop="20250708060200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A 15-year-old rape victim steps off of a subway platform, and two suspects in the case admit to being sexually involved with the girl's mother.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708060200 +0000" stop="20250708070200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A drug dealer dies in jail after being beaten and sexually assaulted.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708070200 +0000" stop="20250708080100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When an 8-year-old beauty queen's body is found in a suitcase on a Manhattan bus, detectives hunt for a pedophile with a fetish for pageants.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708080100 +0000" stop="20250708090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>When a California housewife is murdered in broad daylight, the suspected killer claims it was a burglary gone awry.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708090000 +0000" stop="20250708100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>When a California housewife is murdered in broad daylight, the suspected killer claims it was a burglary gone awry.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708100000 +0000" stop="20250708110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>When Hetty turns in retirement papers and disappears, Shay Mosley comes to Los Angeles to oversee the team and makes staffing changes; Sam insists that Callen find a new partner.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708110000 +0000" stop="20250708120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>When the daughter of a notorious counterfeiter arrives in Los Angeles, Sam goes under cover as a financier; Callen partners with Anna to track the family's latest scheme.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708120000 +0000" stop="20250708130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>During the murder investigation of a Navy Lieutenant on leave in Los Angeles, the team uncovers classified surveillance briefs she smuggled into the city that may have been sold to a foreign buyer.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708130000 +0000" stop="20250708140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Alexandra Cabot questions a pediatrician (Judd Hirsch) about a dead baby found in a cooler in the East River.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708140000 +0000" stop="20250708150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stabler hunts for a missing 14-year-old girl who may have been abducted by a foreign child pornographer.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708150000 +0000" stop="20250708160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives Benson and Stabler look for a killer with a foot fetish.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708160000 +0000" stop="20250708170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A young boy witnesses the brutal sexual assault and murder of his mother.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708170000 +0000" stop="20250708180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A man (Fred Savage) accused of rape becomes a formidable opponent when he decides to handle his own defense.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708180000 +0000" stop="20250708190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Evidence points to an angry ex-boyfriend when a cocktail waitress is murdered outside a popular nightspot.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708190000 +0000" stop="20250708200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives suspect several young socialites of raping a girl at a Manhattan nightclub, then killing her.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708200000 +0000" stop="20250708210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives face off against a Colombian cartel and the Drug Enforcement Administration while investigating the brutal rape and murder of an undercover agent.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708210000 +0000" stop="20250708220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A young woman learning about her birth parents asks Benson for help; Carisi and Rollins weigh the risks of taking their relationship public.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708220000 +0000" stop="20250708230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The creator of a dating app is accused of using it to rape women; Velasco's experience as an SVU detective is put on trial.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250708230000 +0000" stop="20250709000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Velasco asks Benson for help finding three girls who were trafficked from his hometown to New York City.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709000000 +0000" stop="20250709010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Garland asks Benson to reopen a missing persons case he worked as a rookie officer; a victim in one of Carisi's recent cases is arrested.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709010000 +0000" stop="20250709020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When the only evidence in a crime is a church confession, Carisi must find another way to prove his suspect guilty; Benson agrees to meet with an old friend seeking to make amends for past transgressions.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709020000 +0000" stop="20250709030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU provides help and protection for a longtime domestic violence victim, but when she winds up at the defendant's table in court, Rollins surprises Carisi with a formidable opponent at trial.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709030000 +0000" stop="20250709040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A girl is shot and Cosgrove teams with Detective Jalen Shaw to track down her killer; Benson and Stabler assist and realize it's more than a typical homicide; McCoy and Price seek justice against an international crime ring; part 2 of 3.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709040000 +0000" stop="20250709050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A group of teens terrorizing tourists has the SVU squad working overtime; McGrath teams them up with the Bronx gang unit to track down a crucial lead.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709050000 +0000" stop="20250709060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Alexandra Cabot questions a pediatrician (Judd Hirsch) about a dead baby found in a cooler in the East River.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709060000 +0000" stop="20250709070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stabler hunts for a missing 14-year-old girl who may have been abducted by a foreign child pornographer.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709070000 +0000" stop="20250709080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives Benson and Stabler look for a killer with a foot fetish.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709080000 +0000" stop="20250709090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A young boy witnesses the brutal sexual assault and murder of his mother.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709090000 +0000" stop="20250709100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A man (Fred Savage) accused of rape becomes a formidable opponent when he decides to handle his own defense.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709100000 +0000" stop="20250709110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>A series of brutal home invasion robberies finds the team paired with Detective Borkowski, an old friend of Ruzek's, to work the case; things get complicated for Torres when it becomes clear Borkowski has a vastly different policing style.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709110000 +0000" stop="20250709120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>A shocking ambush at a funeral leads the team into a heated investigation to find the shooters; much to Atwater's surprise, he must rely on someone from his past to help in the investigation, dredging up old memories and revealing new truths.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709120000 +0000" stop="20250709130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Sean O'Neal surprises Upton with a call from prison, revealing sensitive information; while Upton grapples with how to keep O'Neal at a distance, the team quickly mobilizes to stop a crime in progress before it's too late.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709130000 +0000" stop="20250709140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Voight and the team help ASA Nina Chapman pursue a drug runner who dodged prison years ago after Chapman's informant mysteriously disappeared; the investigation takes a turn when Voight uncovers a damaging secret from Chapman's past.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709140000 +0000" stop="20250709150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>After a brutal shooting, Burgess and Ruzek find themselves trapped aboard the busy "L" subway; as they piece together scant evidence, the team is drawn into a dark family drama; Burgess' proximity to the shooting triggers harsh memories.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709150000 +0000" stop="20250709160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>When a family is poisoned in their home, the team discovers a connection to the Becks; Ruzek goes undercover to work for their business, and as he gets closer to Samantha, chilling information about her father, Richard, comes to light.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709160000 +0000" stop="20250709170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Voight takes the stand in a high-stakes murder trial against notorious drug kingpin Arturo Morales; when it becomes clear that Morales and his henchmen have compromised a juror, Voight and the team work furiously to ensure justice prevails.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709170000 +0000" stop="20250709180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>An annoying floater takes a romantic interest in Violet; Ritter catches a local politician in a compromising position; Mouch and Severide help Trudy with an arson investigation.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709180000 +0000" stop="20250709190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Kidd, Seager and Carver investigate a fire at the city stables; Kylie clashes with some of the firefighters over changes due to budget cuts; Herrmann struggles to keep it together as Cindy's condition worsens.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709190000 +0000" stop="20250709200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Cruz feels the burden of his increased responsibilities; Kidd, Gallo and Carver get caught in the middle of a gang war on a call; Herrmann wrangles Trudy for help lifting Cindy's mood.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709200000 +0000" stop="20250709210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Mouch builds a classic firetruck model for the Deputy District Chief but needs assistance from Gallo and Ritter; Brett and Violet encounter multiple victims with a strange set of symptoms; Cindy's chemotherapy results loom over the Herrmann family.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709210000 +0000" stop="20250709220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>A familiar face returns to Firehouse 51 to serve with Kidd on a special task force; with Tony close to breaking the CFD's perfect attendance record, Mouch and Capp work to keep him safe; old grudges resurface when Gallo reunites with a family member.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709220000 +0000" stop="20250709230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Boden, Ritter, Herrmann and Kidd work together to take down a local politician responsible for a chemical fire; after his aunt's accident, Gallo worries about their future; Brett steps in to perform Dylan's magic show when he's out of town.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250709230000 +0000" stop="20250710000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Herrmann works on becoming a better man after Cindy's cancer journey; Kidd bonds with a homeless victim on a call; Kylie takes her firefighter exams; a harrowing call takes a toll on Brett.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250710000000 +0000" stop="20250711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ticket to Paradise</title>
    <desc>A man and his ex-wife race to Bali, Indonesia, to stop their daughter from marrying a seaweed farmer. As they desperately try to sabotage the wedding, the bickering duo soon find themselves rekindling old feelings that once made them happy together.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-10</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
