<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250606095421 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403626/20250606.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403626&amp;date=20250606&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606000000 +0000" stop="20250606010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A rape investigation leads to one of Detective Benson's old cases being reopened; as Benson's work is scrutinized, her relationship with Executive ADA David Haden is put in jeopardy.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606010000 +0000" stop="20250606020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A man sees his wife abducted while video chatting with her, but Benson finds that the victim tried to pick up the ransom herself.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606020000 +0000" stop="20250606030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A vigilante group forms in response to a string of rapes; concerns over his wife's fidelity distract Amaro.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606030000 +0000" stop="20250606040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU investigates when a contestant from a reality dating series says she was raped; the producers of the series make Benson and the team part of the show.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606040000 +0000" stop="20250606050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a corrections officer is arrested for sexually assaulting female inmates, the union that supports him set their sights on Barba and the SVU.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606050000 +0000" stop="20250606060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>While the investigation of a corrections officer accused of assaulting female inmates deepens, the union backing the accused man takes action that threatens the lives of the SVU team members.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606060000 +0000" stop="20250606070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson questions Detective Qadri's involvement in the case of a district attorney who fell to her death.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606070000 +0000" stop="20250606080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives Benson and Stabler investigate when a woman scheduled to testify in a high-profile rape case is murdered.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606080000 +0000" stop="20250606090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The detectives are called to investigate when a hotel maid reports being assaulted by a powerful Italian diplomat.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606090000 +0000" stop="20250606100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a dancer is raped by a man with a unique tattoo, details of the case remind Rollins of a serial rapist she was tracking in Atlanta.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606100000 +0000" stop="20250606110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The first responders take calls involving an unusual domestic disturbance, a "death" at a psychic's place, and a motorcycle crash; Bobby dips his toes into the dating pool; Abby walks down memory lane, and Buck is confronted by his past actions.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606110000 +0000" stop="20250606120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Hen relives her evolution into the firefighter she is today as she recalls the first times she met Chimney and Athena.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606120000 +0000" stop="20250606130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>During the holidays, the first responders must deal with a stampede at a toy store, a mistletoe stunt gone awry and neighbors competing in a Christmas light showdown; Bobby contemplates his future with Athena; Chimney and Buck try to help Maddie.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606130000 +0000" stop="20250606140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Bobby meets Athena's parents for the first time; Maddie attempts to end her marriage for good, causing Doug to insinuate himself even deeper into Chimney's life.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606140000 +0000" stop="20250606150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Looking back at how Chimney joined Station 118 and became the firefighter and paramedic he is today.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606150000 +0000" stop="20250606160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The first responders rally together to search for a missing Maddie.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606160000 +0000" stop="20250606170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The call center is hit with a system-wide power outage and must go old school to respond to emergencies; the first responders must deal with explosions in multiple homes and a difficult child birth; Michael confronts Bobby about parenting his kids.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606170000 +0000" stop="20250606180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>When a going-away party for a bank manager turns into an emergency, the first responders are accused of pulling off a daring heist.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606180000 +0000" stop="20250606190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>After his devastating family tragedy in Minnesota, Bobby Nash moves to Los Angeles to start over, where he becomes captain of the 118 and meets Athena Grant for the first time.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606190000 +0000" stop="20250606200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The first responders deal with a calamity at a chocolate factory; a mail bomb explosion; Eddie receives some surprising news from Shannon; Maddie contemplates her future in the call center.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606200000 +0000" stop="20250606210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The team races to save workers in a high-rise during a fire drill, car accident victims, and siblings fighting over a family heirloom; Buck gives Bobby surprising news; Eddie helps Christopher deal with the trauma caused by the tsunami.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606210000 +0000" stop="20250606220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 races to help protesters at a slaughter house and a wife who finds herself trapped in a "rage room" with her husband's mistress; Athena takes action after Michael, May and Harry experience a traumatic traffic stop.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250606220000 +0000" stop="20250607000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">London Has Fallen</title>
    <desc>In London for the Prime Minister's funeral, Mike Banning is caught up in a plot to assassinate all the attending world leaders.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607000000 +0000" stop="20250607030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WWE Friday Night SmackDown</title>
    <desc>The Superstars of World Wrestling Entertainment display their skills and athleticism in weekly episodic programming, as scores are settled and enduring rivalries play out in the ring.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607030000 +0000" stop="20250607040200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry must escape an outer space prison to stop a dangerous threat in town.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607040200 +0000" stop="20250607050300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry and Asta get surprise visits; Ben grows suspicious of Mike and Liv's private investigation.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607050300 +0000" stop="20250607060300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry and Asta team up with an unlikely ally to try to save the Earth.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607060300 +0000" stop="20250607070300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry must escape an outer space prison to stop a dangerous threat in town.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607070300 +0000" stop="20250607080200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>A popular high school student is found murdered in her bed; two students help police solve the case.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607080200 +0000" stop="20250607090100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>When a woman disappears after an encounter on a train, her family hires detectives to investigate.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607090100 +0000" stop="20250607100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>When a woman disappears after an encounter on a train, her family hires detectives to investigate.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607100000 +0000" stop="20250607103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forensic Files</title>
    <desc>Woman disappears from grocery store parking lot in Boulder, Colo.; investigators find extraordinary clues in a pair of bloody gloves, unique tire tracks, and ordinary grass and pine needles.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607103000 +0000" stop="20250607113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Voight's son may be involved with the Fitori murder case, intensifying tension between Antonio and Voight; Ruzek helps Burgess get retribution.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607113000 +0000" stop="20250607123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Voight's new Internal Affairs handler proves to be suspicious of his actions; Voight must work with his former partner from the Gang Unit; Halsted enlists Jin to help him gather more information on Lonnie Rodiger; Olinsky takes Ruzek down a peg.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607123000 +0000" stop="20250607133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Burgess and Atwater come across a gunshot victim and the only witness is Olinsky's daughter; Ruzek goes to Burgess for help with an undercover mission.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607133000 +0000" stop="20250607143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Dueling gangs are suspected when a massacre occurs and $8 million is stolen; Platt asks Ruzek for help.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607143000 +0000" stop="20250607152900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>As Voight and his team search for the bombers, they realize there might be more bombs set to detonate; Burgess' niece fights for her life.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607152900 +0000" stop="20250607180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Olympus Has Fallen</title>
    <desc>Disgraced Secret Service agent Mike Banning finds himself trapped inside the White House in the wake of a terrorist attack and works with national security to rescue the President from his kidnappers.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607180000 +0000" stop="20250607200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">London Has Fallen</title>
    <desc>In London for the Prime Minister's funeral, Mike Banning is caught up in a plot to assassinate all the attending world leaders.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607200000 +0000" stop="20250607230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Black Panther</title>
    <desc>Black Panther's mettle as king gets tested when an old enemy draws him into a conflict that puts his nation and the world at risk. The king must soon rally his allies and release his full power to defeat his foes and secure the safety of his people.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250607230000 +0000" stop="20250608000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Black Panther: Wakanda Forever</title>
    <desc>Queen Ramonda, Shuri, M'Baku, Okoye and the Dora Milaje fight to protect their nation from intervening world powers in the wake of King T'Challa's death.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-07</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
