<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250508113035 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403626/20250508.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403626&amp;date=20250508&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508000000 +0000" stop="20250508023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Creed III</title>
    <desc>Adonis has been thriving in both his career and family life, but when a childhood friend and former boxing prodigy resurfaces, the face-off is more than just a fight.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508023000 +0000" stop="20250508050300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mission: Impossible</title>
    <desc>Branded a traitor, an elite intelligence agent (Tom Cruise) investigates a failed Prague mission to retrieve a computer disk.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508050300 +0000" stop="20250508060300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An investigation into the near-fatal beating of a 12-year-old boy uncovers a female suspect whose trial becomes about the rights of same-sex parents.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508060300 +0000" stop="20250508070100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A mother becomes Stabler and Benson's prime suspect in the poisoning of her child; Novak enlists Clark's assistance in obtaining evidence to remove a judge from the bench after his bias in two child abuse cases leads to a wrongful arrest.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508070100 +0000" stop="20250508080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A video voyeur catches a sexual assault against a minor on tape, which changes the focus of the investigation as the detectives search for a pedophile.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508080000 +0000" stop="20250508090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The son of an outspoken critic becomes the prime suspect when the star of a controversial teen show is raped in her trailer on the set.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508090000 +0000" stop="20250508100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>After recovering from being shot during a robbery, Fin returns to the narcotics division to keep a promise he made to locate a missing person.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508100000 +0000" stop="20250508110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>A truck transporting Christmas trees hits a suspected North Korean spy; Kensi and Deeks try to include their mothers in their plans for Christmas; Hetty thinks Granger is not in the holiday spirit.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508110000 +0000" stop="20250508120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>When a gunnery sergeant moonlighting as a security guard at a decommissioned nuclear power plant suffers radiation poisoning, the team goes under cover to investigate.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508120000 +0000" stop="20250508130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>A tech entrepreneur and venture capitalist who secretly developed a computer program that stealthily collects data is murdered.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508130000 +0000" stop="20250508140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stabler and Fin investigate the brutal rape and murder of a prostitute, and the prime suspects turn out to be a group of teens suspected of re-enacting a favorite video game.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508140000 +0000" stop="20250508150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The detectives discover that a murdered teenage girl was a prostitute and had contracted HIV while working on a pornographic film, which leads them to her killer.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508150000 +0000" stop="20250508160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a wealthy couple laundering money for South American drug dealers is murdered, former ADA Alexandra Cabot (Stephanie March) returns from witness protection to help solve the case.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508160000 +0000" stop="20250508170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stabler struggles to keep his emotions in check as he interrogates a man (Matthew Modine) suspected in the murder of a teenage girl -- a man he once let get away on similar charges.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508170000 +0000" stop="20250508180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A mother who reported the statutory rape of her daughter is found murdered.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508180000 +0000" stop="20250508190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and Stabler have a suspect (Alfred Molina) but not enough evidence when a serial rapist preys on illegal immigrant women, and Tracy Kibre (Bebe Neuwirth) is brought in to work on the case.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508190000 +0000" stop="20250508200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and Stabler probe an assault and carjacking, only to find that it is connected to illegal trafficking in painkillers apparently headed by an elderly woman (Melinda Dillon).</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508200000 +0000" stop="20250508210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When two police officers in separate precincts attack their wives and demonstrate suicidal behavior, Benson and Stabler suspect a malaria drug both men received while serving in a reserve unit in Afghanistan.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508210000 +0000" stop="20250508220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>After a high-school student is brutally assaulted, detectives interview a suspect who becomes enraged and attacks Detective Tutuola.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508220000 +0000" stop="20250508225900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>While searching for a child molester who has abducted three young children orphaned by Hurricane Katrina, detectives learn that the suspect also possesses a deadly strain of anthrax.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508225900 +0000" stop="20250508235700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When an 8-year-old girl is kidnapped on her way home from school, DNA tests on the blood found in the abductor's abandoned van reveal she has leukemia.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250508235700 +0000" stop="20250509000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mission: Impossible</title>
    <desc>Branded a traitor, an elite intelligence agent (Tom Cruise) investigates a failed Prague mission to retrieve a computer disk.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509023000 +0000" stop="20250509043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nobody</title>
    <desc>In a barrage of fists, gunfire and squealing tires, an enraged man must save his wife and son from a dangerous adversary -- and ensure that he will never be underestimated again.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509043000 +0000" stop="20250509053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a baby boy is discovered in the trash, Benson and Stabler use a bar T-shirt found at the scene to link the crime to a well-to-do college student.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509053000 +0000" stop="20250509063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stabler and Fin investigate the brutal rape and murder of a prostitute, and the prime suspects turn out to be a group of teens suspected of re-enacting a favorite video game.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509063000 +0000" stop="20250509073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a wealthy couple laundering money for South American drug dealers is murdered, former ADA Alexandra Cabot (Stephanie March) returns from witness protection to help solve the case.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509073000 +0000" stop="20250509083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stabler struggles to keep his emotions in check as he interrogates a man (Matthew Modine) suspected in the murder of a teenage girl -- a man he once let get away on similar charges.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509083000 +0000" stop="20250509093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A mother who reported the statutory rape of her daughter is found murdered.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509093000 +0000" stop="20250509100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forensic Files</title>
    <desc>A killer is careless when a home is destroyed by fire and a young boy is missing.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509100000 +0000" stop="20250509110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Bobby and the team race to help the survivors of a deadly plane crash; Athena deals with chaos at the airport; Bobby confronts his past demons; Athena is out for revenge against teen bullies; Abby delivers an important message from a 9-1-1 caller.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509110000 +0000" stop="20250509120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The crew races to an emergency at an Indian wedding; Abby enlists Buck to help her find her mother; Abby meets Athena for the first time; Bobby confronts his past; Hen struggles to make the right decision.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509120000 +0000" stop="20250509130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>After his devastating family tragedy in Minnesota, Bobby Nash moves to Los Angeles to start over, where he becomes captain of the 118 and meets Athena Grant for the first time.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509130000 +0000" stop="20250509140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The first responders deal with a calamity at a chocolate factory; a mail bomb explosion; Eddie receives some surprising news from Shannon; Maddie contemplates her future in the call center.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509140000 +0000" stop="20250509150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>A stunt driver is caught in a hairy situation; a teenage social influencer is bugging out; the city is on high alert after two mail bombs go off; Eddie's family comes to town; Buck faces a life-or-death situation.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509150000 +0000" stop="20250509160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 responds to debris from a meteor shower crashing into an apartment building and a deadly fire caused by a hazardous waste truck crash; Hen struggles with guilt over her ambulance accident; Bobby introduces Eddie to an old friend.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509160000 +0000" stop="20250509170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>A man gets pinned under a Humvee; a garage band rocks out too hard; Michael notices strange behavior at a nearby apartment; Hen's mother unexpectedly arrives and announces she is moving to Los Angeles.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509170000 +0000" stop="20250509180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Members of the 118 attempt to rescue a wellness retreat guru after his followers turn on him; an emergency call at an upscale hair salon; Maddie contemplates returning to work, Eddie and May make decisions about their future.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509180000 +0000" stop="20250509190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Athena and Bobby set off on their honeymoon cruise, but when duty calls, their vacation is put on hold; a fighter jet traps a civilian; an unusual incident leaves a couple stuck together.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509190000 +0000" stop="20250509200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The disastrous cruise continues when Bobby and Athena respond to the ship's explosion, racing to aid injured passengers; Hen questions her instincts in a life-taking call and grows concerned about Athena and Bobby's whereabouts.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509200000 +0000" stop="20250509210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>With each moment becoming critical as the ship flips upside down, Athena and Bobby take charge, seeking methods for rescue while navigating efforts to guide survivors to safety; Hen defies protocols in her search for Bobby and Athena.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509210000 +0000" stop="20250509220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>After a victim of the apartment fire that changed Bobby's life resurfaces, he searches to make amends; driven by his need to right past wrongs, Bobby delves deep into memories of his childhood, unearthing moments from his fractured past.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509220000 +0000" stop="20250509230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 and Tommy are presented with the Medal of Valor for their work on the cruise ship rescue; Hen and Karen encounter an unforeseen hurdle in their foster care journey; Eddie's emotional affair develops further.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250509230000 +0000" stop="20250510000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Following the devastating fire at the Nash home, Bobby's fate remains uncertain; Athena embarks on a mission to uncover the truth; Hen and Karin engage in a heated custody battle; Christopher grapples with forgiving Eddie.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250510000000 +0000" stop="20250511000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WWE Friday Night SmackDown</title>
    <desc>The Superstars of World Wrestling Entertainment display their skills and athleticism in weekly episodic programming, as scores are settled and enduring rivalries play out in the ring.</desc>
    <date>2025-05-10</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
