<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250611095655 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403626/20250611.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403626&amp;date=20250611&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611000000 +0000" stop="20250611010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson must disclose the secrets of her past to help a rape victim recall the details of one terrible, traumatic night.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611010000 +0000" stop="20250611020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU investigates a case involving two students in a special needs school; Rollins discovers that one child's medical issues stem from a surprising source.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611020000 +0000" stop="20250611030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Rollins races to rescue a girl being held captive by her father.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611030000 +0000" stop="20250611040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A young woman takes a man hostage at gunpoint; Benson makes an attempt to defuse the situation; the team discovers the shocking motive behind the abduction.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611040000 +0000" stop="20250611050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson's suspicions about a kidnapping victim uncover a dangerous criminal network prepared to silence anyone who gets in its way.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611050000 +0000" stop="20250611060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a masked pizza deliveryman assaults a seemingly random couple in their home, SVU must unravel a complicated revenge plot before anyone else is victimized.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611060000 +0000" stop="20250611070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When an underage runaway is found beaten and raped, the SVU team works with federal prosecutor Connie Rubirosa (Alana De La Garza); ADA Barba suspects a cover-up when he fails to get the help he needs from Jersey law enforcement.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611070000 +0000" stop="20250611080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Amaro suspects the boyfriend of a missing girl is involved with a gang; Sgt. Benson becomes the SVU's new commanding officer.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611080000 +0000" stop="20250611090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a controversial misogynistic comic is accused of rape, Benson is happy to arrest him, but Barba feels the case is weak.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611090000 +0000" stop="20250611100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detective Rollins is contacted by a hometown friend when his nephew, a high school football star, goes missing in New York; Rollins seeks help with her escalating problems.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611100000 +0000" stop="20250611110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey returns to work after a brush with death; Shay's new partner is friendly to everyone but her; Dawson begins training; Severide prepares for his instructor duties; Clarke refuses to talk to the police about the murder.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611110000 +0000" stop="20250611120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey tries to convince everyone he is healthy; Shay avoids the lawyer who wants to talk about Daryl's suicide; Otis and Katie grow closer; Boden helps a woman with a negligent landlord.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611120000 +0000" stop="20250611130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>A call to the field may throw a wrench in Dawson's plan to retake the firefighter exam; the firehouse welcomes a new addition; Boden makes a bold move.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611130000 +0000" stop="20250611140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey deals with the fallout from his sister's divorce; Dawson and Mills settle into their new roles at the station; Brett can't decide what she wants to do; the Molly's crew struggles to get the food truck started.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611140000 +0000" stop="20250611150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey helps his sister and faces down his corrupt brother-in-law; Brett goes out of her way to assist a mother in need; Mills learns about unlicensed private investigation; Dawson starts training with Herrmann.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611150000 +0000" stop="20250611160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey discovers a new crack house on the block that's harboring a female junkie; a new trainee gets Dawson and Brett into trouble; Severide gets an unexpected visit from his father.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611160000 +0000" stop="20250611170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey reunites with a former colleague; Dawson and Brett serve their time in retraining; Severide tries to fix what's going on with Anna.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611170000 +0000" stop="20250611180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Reeling from Dawson's continued absence, Casey makes a rash move during a rescue, while Brett struggles with a series of replacement partners; meanwhile, Boden faces scrutiny from Commissioner Grissom, who sends his deputy to monitor Firehouse 51.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611180000 +0000" stop="20250611190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Mouch, Gallo, Ritter and Mackey report for training; a nasty blow to the head brings Casey unimaginable pain.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611190000 +0000" stop="20250611200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>A series of suspicious fires sends 51 on a search for the cause; Casey continues down a troubling path; Mouch is looking to make his long-awaited dream come true.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611200000 +0000" stop="20250611210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>A new recruit with ties to the CFD tests Serveride's patience; Violet receives a mysterious note that sends her and Brett on a hunt for the person who wrote it.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611210000 +0000" stop="20250611220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Boden, Kidd and Severide work together to protect one of their own; at the Fire Academy, Herrmann meets an inspiring young man; talk of the annual CFD Gala dominates the firehouse.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611220000 +0000" stop="20250611230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide and Seager team up to investigate a fire at the home of a troubled young woman; Pelham moves into 51's rumored cursed office; Kylie assists Kidd with Girls on Fire.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250611230000 +0000" stop="20250612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>After witnessing a domestic dispute, Brett and Violet decide to take the investigation into their own hands; Mouch vets Truck 81's new firefighter; Herrmann relies on something new to aid him on the job.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612000000 +0000" stop="20250612023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Mummy</title>
    <desc>An ancient Egyptian princess is awakened from her crypt beneath the desert, bringing with her malevolence grown over millennia, and terrors that defy human comprehension.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612023000 +0000" stop="20250612050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Twister</title>
    <desc>Storm-chasers (Helen Hunt, Bill Paxton) finalizing their divorce try to place equipment inside a tornado on the Oklahoma plains.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612050000 +0000" stop="20250612060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Resident Alien</title>
    <desc>Harry must escape an outer space prison to stop a dangerous threat in town.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612060000 +0000" stop="20250612070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When Rollins strikes a deal with the managers of a gambling club in order to protect her job, she ends up drawing the suspicion of Benson and Tutuola.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612070000 +0000" stop="20250612080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson is assigned a 24/7 security detail when William Lewis (Pablo Schreiber) escapes from prison and starts killing again; Benson must decide how much she is willing to sacrifice to save a child's life.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612080000 +0000" stop="20250612090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Sgt. Olivia Benson is investigated by Internal Affairs after William Lewis' death; as pressure mounts, Olivia has to choose between her convictions and her badge.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612090000 +0000" stop="20250612100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A teenager disappears after schoolmates make her the subject of a vicious cyberbullying attack.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612100000 +0000" stop="20250612103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forensic Files</title>
    <desc>Two women are murdered in the same town and police fear a serial killer is on the loose, further investigation finds that they were both close to the same man.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612103000 +0000" stop="20250612210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2025 U.S. Open Golf Championship</title>
    <desc>From Oakmont Country Club in Oakmont, Pa.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612210000 +0000" stop="20250612233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Mummy</title>
    <desc>An ancient Egyptian princess is awakened from her crypt beneath the desert, bringing with her malevolence grown over millennia, and terrors that defy human comprehension.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250612233000 +0000" stop="20250613000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Twister</title>
    <desc>Storm-chasers (Helen Hunt, Bill Paxton) finalizing their divorce try to place equipment inside a tornado on the Oklahoma plains.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-12</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
