<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250820110234 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403626/20250820.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403626&amp;date=20250820&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820000000 +0000" stop="20250820010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>As the SVU detectives investigate the alleged rape of a sorority pledge, drunken students and conflicting accounts complicate matters.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820010000 +0000" stop="20250820020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a concert turns into a mob scene, a teenager is brutally assaulted; Detective Amaro ends up defending the prime suspect's reputation.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820020000 +0000" stop="20250820030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When two sniper attacks on the NYPD link to Detective Tutuola's past as a narcotics officer, he reconnects with his former partner in hope of finding a motive; Lt. Alexandra Eames helps SVU investigate.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820030000 +0000" stop="20250820040100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rainmaker</title>
    <desc>Fresh out of law school, Rudy Baylor confronts Leo F. Drummond in a medical malpractice case.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820040100 +0000" stop="20250820050100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The investigation into how a comatose woman ended up in a river near the mayor's home reveals the victim's unexpected wild side.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820050100 +0000" stop="20250820060100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a young boy is abandoned, the squad discovers more victims waiting to be rescued.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820060100 +0000" stop="20250820070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A vigilante group forms in response to a string of rapes; concerns over his wife's fidelity distract Amaro.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820070000 +0000" stop="20250820080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The special victims squad tries to take down a sex-trafficking operation that enslaves young women; when the investigation is halted by Lt. Alexandra Eames (Kathryn Erbe), Detective Benson has to get creative.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820080000 +0000" stop="20250820090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a woman claims that the baby she kidnapped is hers with a respected legal expert, the investigation changes the lives of two families.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820090000 +0000" stop="20250820100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A man goes on a killing spree, but he has links to a prostitute that Benson encountered in an earlier investigation, so the FBI contacts SVU for information.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820100000 +0000" stop="20250820110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Detectives from New York's SVU come to Chicago to help take down a pedophilia ring; Platt shows her respect for the police.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820110000 +0000" stop="20250820120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>When Asher is killed while Antonio is on his security duty, Voight and Olinsky make sure he is covered; Halstead and Lindsay go under cover; Kot wants an answer from Lindsay.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820120000 +0000" stop="20250820130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Following a big heroin bust, Olinsky learns that the suspects are holding his wife hostage; Burgess and Roman get an assignment that pairs them with a K-9 officer: Roman's former partner (Spencer Grammer).</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820130000 +0000" stop="20250820140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>The intelligence team works to find those responsible for Burgess' wounds; a search of the house provides valuable information.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820140000 +0000" stop="20250820150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Lindsay calls on Voight and his unit for help with her first case on the federal task force; Burgess is relegated to desk duty.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820150000 +0000" stop="20250820160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Ruzek's father (Jack Coleman) is first on the scene of a double murder; Lindsay prepares for an undercover investigation in Bolivia; Roman and Burgess try to move forward.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820160000 +0000" stop="20250820170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Antonio and his sister talk to Elliot Gish about the person they think is responsible for the fire that killed Shay; Lindsay has second thoughts about the task force; Platt's new, sunny demeanor results in curiosity.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820170000 +0000" stop="20250820180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide tries to prove his suspicions about the arsonist's identity; Casey gets accustomed to his new lifestyle; Dawson goes on a date with a regular from the bar.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820180000 +0000" stop="20250820190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide wants to implicate the serial arsonist; Dawson and Shay face the unexpected on a routine call; suspicions indicate Clarke is the mole; Mouch campaigns for union president.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820190000 +0000" stop="20250820200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>McLeod pushes Boden toward an early retirement and chooses a potential replacement; all make known their disdain for the mole; Shay enjoys a full social life.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820200000 +0000" stop="20250820210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide comes across a boy in need of help while out on a jog; Boden and McLeod clash over the future of the firehouse; Mouch and Greg Sullivan debate on Otis' podcast.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820210000 +0000" stop="20250820220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>The firehouse crew goes to the scene of a railroad accident; Boden must make a big decision about his future; Severide learns more about the woman he saw with his father; Shay and Dawson continue to butt heads.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820220000 +0000" stop="20250820230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>The shooting of a child in their neighborhood forces Cruz and his brother to think about the gang; Isabella gets Mills to dress up for a gala; Casey feels sad he will be seeing Dawson less; Shay gets in deeper with Devon.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250820230000 +0000" stop="20250821000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Boden tries to keep the firehouse from closing; the romance between Dawson and Casey grows; Cruz worries for his brother's safety; Severide and Katie make up for lost time.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821000000 +0000" stop="20250821030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">National Treasure</title>
    <desc>An adventurer (Nicolas Cage) must steal the Declaration of Independence and use its hidden map to find a legendary fortune.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821030000 +0000" stop="20250821040100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rainmaker</title>
    <desc>Fresh out of law school, Rudy Baylor confronts Leo F. Drummond in a medical malpractice case.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821040100 +0000" stop="20250821050100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Chief Boden leads the fight to keep the firehouse open; an emergency call to an apartment structure puts the squad in harm's way; Dawson receives life-changing news.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821050100 +0000" stop="20250821060100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey returns to work after a brush with death; Shay's new partner is friendly to everyone but her; Dawson begins training; Severide prepares for his instructor duties; Clarke refuses to talk to the police about the murder.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821060100 +0000" stop="20250821070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The detectives investigate when woman visiting from Buffalo, N.Y., claims her car was stolen with her baby in the backseat.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821070000 +0000" stop="20250821080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a young mail-order bride is found dead, the investigation leads the detectives to the Russian mafia.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821080000 +0000" stop="20250821090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives Benson and Rollins investigate when a mental patient says he witnessed a rape, but the alleged victim denies the assault happened.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821090000 +0000" stop="20250821100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a child disappears on his way home from school, Benson and Amaro interview the distraught parents, who don't trust the police; with the help of their TARU tech (Gilbert Gottfried) and a meddling reporter, the detectives narrow the suspects list.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821100000 +0000" stop="20250821110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>An elaborate bank heist to steal a single safe deposit box held by a Navy contractor leads NCIS to investigate her corrupt consulting firm.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821110000 +0000" stop="20250821120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>The NCIS team searches for a Marine reservist with a history of post-traumatic stress disorder who disappears following a drunk and disorderly altercation.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821120000 +0000" stop="20250821130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>The team investigates a possible terror threat after the chief of logistics for a naval weapons station collapses on the job; Kensi and Deeks research different honeymoon locations.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821130000 +0000" stop="20250821140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When the investigation into a missing teen leads the detectives to a severed leg, they are drawn into the world of self-mutilation and ritual amputation.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821140000 +0000" stop="20250821150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A promising singer is beaten by her boyfriend, a famous hip-hop star, but she refuses to help ADA Barba build his case; the defendant and his attorney turn the case into a media circus.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821150000 +0000" stop="20250821160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Investigation into the suspected rape of a woman Benson helped earlier leads to a cybermogul; the team bids farewell to Sgt. Munch.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821160000 +0000" stop="20250821170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>ADA Barba finds that a friend (Kirk Acevedo) -- with a connection to a mayoral candidate frontrunner -- is accused of rape.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821170000 +0000" stop="20250821180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a suspect is gravely injured and the case becomes a public spectacle, Amaro's badge is on the line; Cragen surprises everyone with an announcement.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821180000 +0000" stop="20250821190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When an underage runaway is found beaten and raped, the SVU team works with federal prosecutor Connie Rubirosa (Alana De La Garza); ADA Barba suspects a cover-up when he fails to get the help he needs from Jersey law enforcement.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821190000 +0000" stop="20250821200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Amaro suspects the boyfriend of a missing girl is involved with a gang; Sgt. Benson becomes the SVU's new commanding officer.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821200000 +0000" stop="20250821210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The already frantic search for a missing diabetic boy becomes more urgent when he is spotted with a couple known for child endangerment and pornography.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821210000 +0000" stop="20250821220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a controversial misogynistic comic is accused of rape, Benson is happy to arrest him, but Barba feels the case is weak.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821220000 +0000" stop="20250821230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detective Rollins is contacted by a hometown friend when his nephew, a high school football star, goes missing in New York; Rollins seeks help with her escalating problems.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250821230000 +0000" stop="20250822000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When Rollins strikes a deal with the managers of a gambling club in order to protect her job, she ends up drawing the suspicion of Benson and Tutuola.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250822000000 +0000" stop="20250823000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">National Treasure: Book of Secrets</title>
    <desc>A page from the diary of John Wilkes Booth implicates Ben Gates' (Nicolas Cage) great-great grandfather as a major conspirator in the assassination of President Lincoln.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-22</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
