<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250828090031 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403626/20250828.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403626&amp;date=20250828&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828020000 +0000" stop="20250828050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jurassic World Dominion</title>
    <desc>Four years after the destruction of Isla Nublar, Biosyn operatives attempt to track down Maisie Lockwood, while Dr Ellie Sattler investigates a genetically engineered swarm of giant insects.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828050000 +0000" stop="20250828060100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rainmaker</title>
    <desc>Rudy and Deck have a tense encounter with a witness and make a crucial discovery about their client.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828060100 +0000" stop="20250828070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A tourist is found dead with the word "guilty" written on her forehead; Detective Munch is forced to ask his ex-wife (Carol Kane) for help.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828070000 +0000" stop="20250828080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The media spotlight shines on Sgt. Benson when she investigates a string of rapes that have similarities with crimes in Atlanta; a family court judge threatens to remove baby Noah from Benson's care.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828080000 +0000" stop="20250828090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>After being found unconscious in her hotel bathroom, an Atlanta detective -- in town for a law-enforcement conference -- says that she was raped; Rollins discovers a personal connection to the suspect.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828090000 +0000" stop="20250828100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When Amaro's estranged father (Armand Assante) is arrested at his own wedding, Amaro becomes a witness and secrets threaten to tear their family apart.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828100000 +0000" stop="20250828110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>The NCIS team investigates the murder of a journalist who was writing an exposé on a mishandled classified military operation; as their wedding day quickly approaches, Kensi and Deeks work on the last remaining items on their to-do list.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828110000 +0000" stop="20250828120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>After months of planning, the NCIS family celebrates the wedding of Kensi and Deeks; an old acquaintance pays Deeks a surprise visit on his wedding day.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828120000 +0000" stop="20250828130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>Sydney turns to her sister Nell for help after her high school crush gets mixed up in a Russian plot to steal intelligence from the Department of Defense; Special Prosecutor John Rogers conducts mandatory performance reviews with the team.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828130000 +0000" stop="20250828140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Taking an active approach to catching sex offenders, the team targets a photographer with a secret life whose fantasies may have crossed into reality.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828140000 +0000" stop="20250828150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Amaro must face the consequence of his reckless behavior; when an online ad for escorts leads to the rape and robbery of tourists, Benson discovers she has a connection to one of the suspects.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828150000 +0000" stop="20250828160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson struggles to balance work and her new role of foster mother; when Amaro arrests a young prostitute with connections to Noah's mother, his undercover work sets off a dangerous chain of events.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828160000 +0000" stop="20250828170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a series of allegations are made against a superstar basketball player, Sgt. Benson and Detective Carisi (Peter Scanavino) do not agree on the authenticity of each woman's story; the investigation takes Rollins back to her former precinct.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828170000 +0000" stop="20250828180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Amaro's by-the-book handling of a starlet's arrest gets him back on the SVU squad in time to investigate the actress's latest offense, statutory rape.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828180000 +0000" stop="20250828190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>During an interview on a popular TV show, a college student claims she was gang raped in a fraternity, bringing national attention to rape on campus; Benson and Barba investigate multiple suspects.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828190000 +0000" stop="20250828200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When Johnny D (Charles Halford) is on trial for sex trafficking, rape, assault and kidnapping, Noah's adoption becomes involved with the case, causing Benson to fear for the child's future; a threat could permanently change the squad.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828200000 +0000" stop="20250828210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a starving toddler is found wandering the streets, detectives are led to a home where another child is in grave condition; Chief Dodds (Peter Gallagher) suggests that Benson's squad may be undergoing changes.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828210000 +0000" stop="20250828220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An unarmed black man is shot during the pursuit of a suspect, raising racial tensions; Barba must indict the three officers involved -- who claim they followed procedure.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828220000 +0000" stop="20250828230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The search for a missing teenager takes an emotional toll on Dodds; DNA evidence could lead to the teen's abductor.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250828230000 +0000" stop="20250829000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The futures of two high-school students are complicated by a murky date-rape case filled with dueling accusations.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829000000 +0000" stop="20250829010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a woman is followed home and raped outside of her building, neighbors witness the crime but neglect to call for help.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829010000 +0000" stop="20250829050200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Green Mile</title>
    <desc>In 1935 a head prison guard (Tom Hanks) realizes a man (Michael Clarke Duncan) on death row may be innocent and have a supernatural ability to heal others.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829050200 +0000" stop="20250829060200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Taking an active approach to catching sex offenders, the team targets a photographer with a secret life whose fantasies may have crossed into reality.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829060200 +0000" stop="20250829070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Amaro must face the consequence of his reckless behavior; when an online ad for escorts leads to the rape and robbery of tourists, Benson discovers she has a connection to one of the suspects.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829070000 +0000" stop="20250829080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson struggles to balance work and her new role of foster mother; when Amaro arrests a young prostitute with connections to Noah's mother, his undercover work sets off a dangerous chain of events.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829080000 +0000" stop="20250829090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Amaro's by-the-book handling of a starlet's arrest gets him back on the SVU squad in time to investigate the actress's latest offense, statutory rape.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829090000 +0000" stop="20250829100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>During an interview on a popular TV show, a college student claims she was gang raped in a fraternity, bringing national attention to rape on campus; Benson and Barba investigate multiple suspects.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829100000 +0000" stop="20250829140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Green Mile</title>
    <desc>In 1935 a head prison guard (Tom Hanks) realizes a man (Michael Clarke Duncan) on death row may be innocent and have a supernatural ability to heal others.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829140000 +0000" stop="20250829150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The team races to save workers in a high-rise during a fire drill, car accident victims, and siblings fighting over a family heirloom; Buck gives Bobby surprising news; Eddie helps Christopher deal with the trauma caused by the tsunami.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829150000 +0000" stop="20250829160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 races to help protesters at a slaughter house and a wife who finds herself trapped in a "rage room" with her husband's mistress; Athena takes action after Michael, May and Harry experience a traumatic traffic stop.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829160000 +0000" stop="20250829170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Athena and the 118 respond to bizarre emergency calls on Halloween, including a flock of crows terrorizing a field trip, an office employee having a close encounter with an eight-limbed creature and a ghost-like girl wandering a neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829170000 +0000" stop="20250829180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>When a murder weapon from a case close to Athena in the early '90s resurfaces, flashbacks to 1989 show how Athena joined the LAPD and became the police officer she is today.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829180000 +0000" stop="20250829190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>A skating mishap at an ice show; an accident involving a self-driving car; a fulfillment warehouse robot goes rogue; Eddie's after-hours fight club gets out of control; Hen struggles in her relationship with Karen.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829190000 +0000" stop="20250829200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 responds to debris from a meteor shower crashing into an apartment building and a deadly fire caused by a hazardous waste truck crash; Hen struggles with guilt over her ambulance accident; Bobby introduces Eddie to an old friend.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829200000 +0000" stop="20250829210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Holiday-themed incidents include a shopper pushed over the edge, a woman who is literally having a "Blue Christmas" and a luggage handler accident on a tarmac; Maddie revisits her past to embrace her future; Bobby receives shocking news.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829210000 +0000" stop="20250829220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 responds to a skydiving trip gone wrong; a bank rep is injured in a home repossession; a lovestruck assistant's lunch run ends in disaster; Athena and the family come to terms with Michael's difficult health decision.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829220000 +0000" stop="20250829230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 responds to a viral stunt gone haywire, a disaster at a couple's fishing trip and an epic first date fail; Athena investigates a woman who doesn't remember being shot in the head; Eddie must have a difficult conversation with Christopher.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250829230000 +0000" stop="20250830000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Accidents happen at a bowling alley and a home renovation; Athena pursues a car thief; Bobby and Michael take Harry camping; Chimney and Maddie rush into action when their romantic dinner date takes a wild turn.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250830000000 +0000" stop="20250831000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WWE Friday Night SmackDown</title>
    <desc>The Superstars of World Wrestling Entertainment display their skills and athleticism in weekly episodic programming, as scores are settled and enduring rivalries play out in the ring.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-30</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
