<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250826100027 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403626/20250826.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403626&amp;date=20250826&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403626">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network - East Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826000000 +0000" stop="20250826010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a female video game developer who has been receiving death threats refuses to delay the launch of her new game, the cops must work to protect her.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826010000 +0000" stop="20250826020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>While working under cover to bust a sex trafficking ring, Carisi meets a woman who embedded herself in the organization in hope of finding and saving her daughter; Sgt. Benson is faced with a life-changing revelation.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826020000 +0000" stop="20250826030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A feud between a famous author (Robert Vaughn) and his sixth wife, Charmaine (Marcia Cross), turns into a criminal case when Charmaine is faced with allegations of abuse; Barba winds up dealing with family drama of his own.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826030000 +0000" stop="20250826040100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rainmaker</title>
    <desc>Rudy and Deck have a tense encounter with a witness and make a crucial discovery about their client.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826040100 +0000" stop="20250826050100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A woman wants to recant her testimony and free her father, who was incarcerated for incest and rape when she was a child; Capt. Cragen, who remembers the original investigation, tries to help the team.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826050100 +0000" stop="20250826060100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Efforts to find an 8-year-old boy kidnapped for ransom are hindered by tension between the child's estranged parents; Sgt. Benson is asked to take the lieutenant's exam and officially become the leader of the squad.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826060100 +0000" stop="20250826070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>After a single mom is arrested for leaving her young daughter alone for days, Sgt. Benson suspects the woman may have been abused in her own childhood.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826070000 +0000" stop="20250826080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Three young girls' search for a mythical character leads to one of them becoming injured and the other two disappearing.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826080000 +0000" stop="20250826090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>The sister of a man who died after robbing a bank when a bomb that was placed around his neck detonated talks about the case.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826090000 +0000" stop="20250826100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>The sister of a man who died after robbing a bank when a bomb that was placed around his neck detonated talks about the case.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826100000 +0000" stop="20250826110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>The team works with the Global Criminal Tribunal when a Syrian is attacked while delivering evidence that would prove chemical weapons were used on civilians; Kensi stays at the crime scene and comforts Sarraf, who is pinned behind a vehicle.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826110000 +0000" stop="20250826120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>The NCIS team partners with the FBI to locate a terrorist cell in Los Angeles believed to be preparing for an imminent attack.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826120000 +0000" stop="20250826130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>The team continues to search for a terrorist cell in Los Angeles; Callen and Sam remain trapped in a movie theater after multiple bombs have detonated, and every remaining exit is wired with explosives.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826130000 +0000" stop="20250826140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stabler fears a combative Benson will be the next victim of a real estate agent suspected of sexually assaulting and murdering a lawyer.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826140000 +0000" stop="20250826150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The details of a kidnapping are similar to a series of rapes and murders that may link the crime to a serial killer.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826150000 +0000" stop="20250826160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Three people, unconnected except to cases that Detective Benson investigated, are found ritualistically murdered.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826160000 +0000" stop="20250826170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A murdered 14-year-old girl leads the detectives to a prominent physician who specializes in reproduction therapy.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826170000 +0000" stop="20250826180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>While examining a 9-year-old girl after a car crash, doctors find that she has been molested and call in Benson and Stabler, who learn that the girl's attacker has killed another child.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826180000 +0000" stop="20250826190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A young Jewish boy is brutally attacked, and the clues lead to a disturbed classmate as more victims begin to come forward.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826190000 +0000" stop="20250826200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The theft of fertilized embryos from a sperm bank leads the detectives to two publicity-hungry extremists.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826200000 +0000" stop="20250826210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A tourist is found dead with the word "guilty" written on her forehead; Detective Munch is forced to ask his ex-wife (Carol Kane) for help.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826210000 +0000" stop="20250826220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A case becomes much more complicated when racy photos of a 15-year-old rape victim are leaked on the Internet; Stabler's son is drawn into a series of compromising events by his best friend.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826220000 +0000" stop="20250826230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>DNA evidence points to Benson as the prime suspect when the sexually mutilated body of a member of a biker gang is found in the park; Stabler fights to prove his partner's innocence.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250826230000 +0000" stop="20250827000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A famous TV host (Roger Bart) forces himself on the young author (Anna Chlumsky) of an erotic novel; Detective Amaro uncovers a secret that could damage the author's career and her case.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827000000 +0000" stop="20250827010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An investigation into the sexual exploitation of Catholic schoolgirls results in charges against judges, legislators, DAs and members of the police department.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827010000 +0000" stop="20250827020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The team works to unravel a sex trafficking operation with ties to government offices, the police department and the Catholic church after one of their own is implicated in a cover-up.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827020000 +0000" stop="20250827030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>SVU investigates the assault, murder and mutilation of a member of a women's empowerment group; Fin and Carisi wonder who the father of Rollins' baby is.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827030000 +0000" stop="20250827040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The squad rallies around Det. Stabler to find the suspect behind a threat to his family.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827040000 +0000" stop="20250827050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>FBI Agent Dana Lewis partners with SVU when she thinks a 25-year-old rape-murder case in New York is connected to multiple unsolved cases across the country; as Lewis doggedly pursues her suspect, Benson and Amaro question his guilt.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827050000 +0000" stop="20250827060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The team tries to find a bike messenger -- who has kept a video diary of his troubles with women -- before he can commit another violent act; the new deputy chief calls Benson's leadership into question.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827060000 +0000" stop="20250827070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stabler fears a combative Benson will be the next victim of a real estate agent suspected of sexually assaulting and murdering a lawyer.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827070000 +0000" stop="20250827080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>While examining a 9-year-old girl after a car crash, doctors find that she has been molested and call in Benson and Stabler, who learn that the girl's attacker has killed another child.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827080000 +0000" stop="20250827090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A young Jewish boy is brutally attacked, and the clues lead to a disturbed classmate as more victims begin to come forward.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827090000 +0000" stop="20250827100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The theft of fertilized embryos from a sperm bank leads the detectives to two publicity-hungry extremists.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827100000 +0000" stop="20250827110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Bunny comes to Lindsay with a concern that leads the team to a case that robbery-homicide has been investigating; Voight is suspicious of Bunny's motives.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827110000 +0000" stop="20250827120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Burgess and Roman become trapped after Burgess pursues suspicious activity at a convenience store without calling in for backup; the intelligence team receives taser certification.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827120000 +0000" stop="20250827130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>When an undercover narcotics officer goes missing, Antonio is asked to help find him; Burgess and Roman ask Mouch (Christian Stolte) for help with a squatter situation.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827130000 +0000" stop="20250827140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>The members of intelligence go under cover at a World Trade conference to assess political threats; Halstead's brother immediately stirs up trouble when he shows up in town.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827140000 +0000" stop="20250827150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>An investigation into a drug robbery gone wrong reveals Voight has ties to a teen linked to a double murder; Desk Sgt. Platt cares for a young girl.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827150000 +0000" stop="20250827160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>A case involving one of Chicago's most wanted fugitives hits close to home with Olinsky; an altercation with another officer lands Sean Roman in hot water; Platt helps Nadia prepare for her polygraph test.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827160000 +0000" stop="20250827170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>After arriving in Chicago to assist Voight and the team with a rape/murder case that has distinct similarities to a decade-old case from New York, Sgt. Benson asks Fin and Amaro to help; the prime suspect asks for a meeting with Lindsay.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827170000 +0000" stop="20250827180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Casey tries to convince everyone he is healthy; Shay avoids the lawyer who wants to talk about Daryl's suicide; Otis and Katie grow closer; Boden helps a woman with a negligent landlord.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827180000 +0000" stop="20250827190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>A drunken driver takes out a transformer, leaving the entire neighborhood without power on a frigid night; Casey continues to lie about his condition.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827190000 +0000" stop="20250827200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide must leave Lindsay and the Intelligence Unit to find Katie; Blackhawk players Brent Seabrook and Duncan Keith give Shay a tip; Casey gets more information about his head injuries; Dawson works to pass the physical test.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827200000 +0000" stop="20250827210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide becomes frustrated with the police; a girl is trapped in a donation bin; a fire breaks out in a 20-story building downtown.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827210000 +0000" stop="20250827220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Detective Lindsay calls in suspects in the disappearance of Katie's kidnapper; Jones struggles to fit in; Herrmann celebrates his 20th wedding anniversary.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827220000 +0000" stop="20250827230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide feels compelled to help a man he saved from a car accident; Casey and Boden struggle to deal with the orders from Jones' father; a call to duty affects the firehouse.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403626" start="20250827230000 +0000" stop="20250828000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jurassic World Dominion</title>
    <desc>Four years after the destruction of Isla Nublar, Biosyn operatives attempt to track down Maisie Lockwood, while Dr Ellie Sattler investigates a genetically engineered swarm of giant insects.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-27</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
